So, we just give it a photo of any
product and we ask it to create, let's
say, 25 videos. And once that's done, we
get the videos back ready to post.
>> So, Tik Tok made me buy this and it
turns out it's the best tasting fruit
beer in Sydney. And they donate their
profits to charity. And you know what?
It's honestly really good.
>> So, Tik Tok made me buy this
>> and it turns out it's the best tasting
fruit beer in Sydney.
>> And they donate their profits to
charity.
>> And you know what? It's honestly really
good. So, I saw these on Tik Tok and
after a few weeks, my yoga recovery
feels way better. And now I feel way
more focused for my classes. Maybe it's
the fish oil. They really help me with
my yoga. Like my joints just feel less
stiff now. I swear. So I saw this on Tik
Tok. Everyone was obsessed with this
book and honestly it's changing how I
build my habits. For real.
>> I just built this AI system that creates
infinite UGC style ads for any product
or brand completely on autopilot. You
just tell it how many videos you want,
describe the influencers that you want
in your videos, either give them a
script or have the system write it for
you, and it generates all of those UGC
ads ready for you to post. Because if,
in case you don't know, today's brands
are launching ads literally by the
hundreds in order to test which creative
works, and it's powered by AI systems
like these. So once you learn this
skill, you can use it for your own
product. Offer it as a service for
clients who need content or UGC with
some client acquisition techniques
explained near the end of the video or
even earn passive affiliate income by
driving traffic to Amazon products.
What's crazy is each of these videos
only costs 43 cents to make, which is
orders of magnitude cheaper versus
spending it on influencers for the same
type of content. And remember, what you
saw in the demo is the worst that it
will ever be because as time goes on,
the quality of these will only go up and
the cost will slowly go down. So, if
you're serious about taking advantage of
the historic shift that AI is bringing,
and with demand for AI agents and
automation rising fast, if you just
check Google Trends, then picking up the
skill to make these AI systems, which
are all no code anyway, so anyone can
learn them, is bound to pay off for you
in a big way. So, if you have the time,
invest some today to listen to the end
so that you too can master this
increasingly important AI skill. Let's
get started.
If you're new here, my name is Jay. I
run my own AI creative agency where we
help mostly brands and content
businesses use AI in meaningful ways.
And I also founded the RoboNuggets
community. We have several hundred
members now who are all AI practitioners
and builders located across the globe.
And here our mission is simple is to
make creating with AI easy to learn for
anyone who wants to. That's why in all
of our videos, I make sure to go through
each note so that you can also
understand the principles of creating
automations and AI systems like this one
that I'm about to show you. But cool,
let's dive into this. So essentially
this AI system, the way that you use it
is sort of like a mini application. So
whenever you need, let's say, UGC ads or
content for your product or for your
client's product, what you do is you go
in here and the only thing that you need
to tweak would be this node right here,
which is the creative brief because if
we open that and if we just zoom in,
this is essentially where we provide all
of the building blocks for our AI agent
to create those UDC ads for us. So, at
the very top, we have here the field for
the reference image that we are going to
feed this model. And if we open this
link, essentially what you'll find is a
photo that I took of this Four Pines
Brewing Company beer, which we will be
using as a demo product for this
tutorial. And then if we just scroll
down here, there's just a few fields
around how many videos that you want.
So, for this run, we'll create three UGC
videos, although you can increase that
or make that into one. And then we have
this section for the dialogue. So, if
you have a specific script in mind, this
is where you put it. Or if you want the
agent to ideulate the script, you can
just direct it like so and the agent
will actually understand that. But for
this one, we'll just give it this
specific copy. And then the model, we
just set it as V3 fast, which is the
cheaper model between V3. And then we
just have a few more fields here, which
we'll go through in a bit around what
model to use and what aspect ratio to
deliver it as. And you'll see that is
vertical, and a free text field around
any special requests. And we'll go
through this together in a bit. But once
you have set these up on your side, that
is pretty much all the setup you need in
order to create those UGC ads. So now if
we execute this workflow, it will handle
all the technical heavy lifting for you
to create the prompts that you need for
those three or however many videos that
you want to create as well as the video
generation which this ads factory will
be handling automatically. So when that
workflow has finished, it will upload
all of your videos in the cloud storage
of your choice. For this one, we just
use box because it is quite easy to set
up. And if we go there, you can see that
we have those three videos now
generated. And this is just one of the
examples.
>> So, Tik Tok made me buy this and it
turns out it's the best tasting fruit
beer in Sydney and they donate their
profits to charity.
>> So, that looks really good. So, more
importantly, how does this whole thing
work? We basically have just one picture
of a product and out comes a really good
UGC video which you can even define how
many you want or which actors that you
want. Well, what we're going to do next
is I'll just go through each of these
nodes so that you can also understand
the principles of how to set this up
yourself as well as some of the thinking
and prompt engineering that went behind
this particularly for this AI agent
node. But very quickly, just the
structure of this workflow is quite
simple because like a lot of the
templates we showed here, we always have
this input section where we arrange the
elements for our AI agent to work with.
And then we have this configuration or
factory section where we create the
prompts here in this area. We pass it
along to our image and video generation
model and then out comes our output
which is the UGC video that we store in
box or whatever storage solution that
you are after. So starting with the
input section you can see that the
trigger here is manual and the reason
why that is is for a lot of these
creative workflows what we're actually
finding is that we're using them as sort
of like a mini application where
basically they generate the ads for us
on demand. You can obviously schedule
this and connect this whole thing to
autopublishing automations like blot
which we featured a lot in this channel
but at least for this case this is more
like a production machine rather than a
postcheduling workflow but anyway we
already went through this edit fields
node but just a couple of things that we
haven't covered in our demo earlier. So
if you open this and if you're new to NN
basically the way that this works is
there's always an input area here that
are all the data that's coming from
previous nodes. You have the
configuration of your node here and then
here at the right is the output section
which gives you a preview of the values
that this node is passing along to the
next ones. Now here as mentioned we have
the G drive link for the reference image
which as we showed is just a normal G
drive link. Now to set this up it's very
simple. So on your Google Drive you just
want to create a folder like what I did
here and then just make sure that you
share this whole folder for anyone with
the link. And the reason why you want
that is so that N8N can actually access
the images that you put in here. So you
can see that I have a couple of product
images that I took here as an example
and as a test. This is the one we were
using. And so all I did to get that link
is to just copy that link and place that
here. So that is very simple. And then
here we declare how many videos we need.
So for this run we've set it as three.
And then for the dialogue as mentioned
you can either have a specific dialogue
or you can also have your AI agent think
of the script for you. So in fact for
this walkth through let's do that. So
let's type something like please suggest
a script that will highlight this
product's fruity flavor. And that works
because when that's passed along to your
AI agent they'll be able to understand
that direction as well. Now for the
model again this is sort of like a free
text field because when we pass this
along to the AI agent all the agent
really is doing is to choose between V3
fast or V3 quality. And basically the
difference is V3 is a higher quality but
is five times more expensive. So with
the method we'll show V3 is actually $2
per video while VO3 fast is only 40
cents for that 8-second clip. And in my
experience V3 is not actually five times
better in quality. It's only marginally
better. So for a lot of use cases I
think V3 fast already is enough. So
we'll leave that be. And then for the
aspect ratio you can dictate this as
vertical. In fact, even if you tell it
as portrait, the agent will understand
it as well. Or you can also have this as
landscape. So just to be different,
let's do a landscape one for this
specific run. And then we have a free
text field here for any special requests
as I showed earlier. Now if we just
expand that, you'll see that we just
have a few inputs here where we're
saying that we want normal and casual
looking people. You can also define the
age range here and also have diversity
in the actor's gender. So this is the
area where you can have the freedom to
brief your agent with whatever that you
want. So for example, for this run, have
all of the actors
be in their cars. And then here I also
defined some common scenes when it comes
to UGC. You can opt not to have this or
also add a few more if you wish, but
you'll see that we just have a few
scenes here describing a person in a
podcast, person in their car, an
everyday mirror selfie, and so on and so
forth. So you can read through that in
your own time, but that's just a way for
us to give our agent an idea of what
we're looking for is what this edit
fields node is about. And so if we
execute this step, all that really does
is load all of that input data into its
run for this one. So if you go to
schema, everything here is just what we
defined for our agent. So that's pretty
good. So now if you click away, the next
node here is an analyze image node. So
if you open that, you can see we just
have it connected to our OpenAI account
as a credential which we've featured
several times in our channel how to do
that credential piece. And the operation
that we are doing here is for us to
analyze the image that we got from
Google Drive. And the reason why we're
doing that is because as of the moment
N8N's AI agent node cannot actually
understand images yet. And so we just
need this preceding node in order to
feed it information around the image or
the visual that we're passing it. So if
you look at the command we just gave it,
essentially we're just asking it to
return its analysis in a format that is
quite detailed. So we're asking ChachPT
to identify what the brand name is, what
the color scheme is, the font style,
what the visual description is of the
image we just passed along to it. And
here under the URL is where we pass
along that said image. Now you can see
that there's a bit of a character salad
here. And the reason why we need to do
that is because with Google Drive, this
link that you just gave N8N is actually
not going to function by itself because
it's not a direct download link. And so
all we are really doing here is provide
that special syntax for Google Drive. So
that we're simply getting the ID of this
particular image and as a result we get
this final URL which if you paste to
your browser that will just
automatically download that image which
if you look at it from N8N's point of
view that is what you need in order to
run this step. So if we execute this
step, what it's going to do is to look
at that four pines beer image. And as an
output, if we just go to the table view
and under the content, you can see here
that we now have that brand name loaded
into N8N in text format. It even gave us
the color palette in hex code, the font
style, and the visual description, which
is what we need to inform our agent of
what's going to happen next. So that is
basically all the input section now
done. Now all of the magic here mostly
happens with the AI agent and so this
node if you open it up you'll see that
with any AI agent you have a user prompt
which is sort of like what you send to
chat GPT and then you have a system
prompt which is sort of the underlying
instructions on how this agent behaves
and what its role in life is. So if we
just go to the user prompt and open that
you'll find that we gave it a task to
create an image and video prompt as
guided by your system guidelines which
we'll go through later. Now apart from
that we also gave it a few things which
we arranged for it neatly earlier. We
gave it the count of videos to create
and you can see all of these green
values which means they are dynamic
values and so this is mapping to how
many videos that you declared earlier
and so if you remember we declared three
videos there. We also gave it the
description of the reference image which
is coming from the previous step and you
can see how it translates here which is
what we just saw earlier and also gave
it the user's preferred aspect ratio,
the user's preferred model and dialogue
script and other special requests from
the user. So if you look at the
resulting values here for this run,
these are exactly what we declared
earlier. So we want a landscape video.
We want to use this model. We want it to
suggest a script. And finally a couple
of special requests that we declared
during that very first node. And so that
is our request. Now the system message
is the one that is basically dictating
how this model behaves. And this is
quite detailed. So I'll just go through
the specific points. But if you look at
this at the very top, we just have an
overarching direction here around it
being a UDC AI agent. what its task is,
which is basically taking the reference
image or the product in the reference
image and placing it into realistic
casual scenes and some extra guidelines
there in order to make it more natural.
Now, this part is important because if
you want a realistic looking video, you
actually need to add these sorts of
prompts like unremarkable amateur iPhone
photos or else it may look unrealistic
in the end. This is where we declare to
the agent that if the dialogue is not
provided then please generate that. So,
you'll see that in action in a bit. And
then we have a couple of guidelines here
because if you use an ellipses, that is
actually good in V3 to indicate pauses.
And if you have special characters like
m dashes or hyphens in the text, that
sometimes shows off the dialogue. So,
it's just good to make sure that the AI
agent doesn't include that in the
prompts. And then we also have an
avoidance for double quotes because that
introduces problems when we are
prompting with APIs. And then we have
here the agent framework of our ask
which we are just finding is good
practice when it comes to creating
system prompts. So we made a video of
that a few weeks ago if you're curious
about this topic. But basically what
that means is to provide an agent with
your ask which is what you want it to
output to you some guidance some
examples the notation which is important
so that the structure it provides you is
consistent as well as the tools that it
has access to. So just to point out some
of the ones that we haven't covered yet.
I think the ask is mostly the same. We
just added this scene count rule which
is basically accommodating for the fact
that maybe the user wants only one scene
or maybe three scenes or did not declare
anything at all. We provided it some
guidance which is mostly just a repeat
and a reinforcement of the ones we
highlighted at the top. And this one's
important some examples so that it knows
what we are looking for in terms of the
structure there. So you'll see that more
in a bit once we run this. And then the
notation, you can read this in your own
time. But basically what this is saying
is for each scene, please give us an
image prompt, a video prompt, the aspect
ratio for the video, which is either 9x6
or 16x9, and an aspect ratio for the
image, which is these values. So these
are coming from just the allowed values
of the image and video models we are
going to use. And this is also where the
model choices are declared. So that's
good. And then we just have the think
tool here, which you'll see in a bit.
Basically, that allows the agent to
doublech checkck its output before
giving it to you. So, very detailed
system prompt. That's what it takes in
order to make this agent really smart
and run on its own on autopilot. And if
you click away, you'll see that the
tools it has access to is pretty much
standard. We are just using GPT4.1. We
have the think tool that we referenced
earlier. Didn't really change anything
here. This is the default but just
adding it there will allow the agent to
sort of reason and think about its
output before finalizing it. And then
most importantly you have the structured
output which is where you declare that
final output structure that you want the
agent to adhere to. Right? So this is
just similar to what we went through in
that notation section. So lots of setup
and prompt engineering that happened
there. But now if we execute this step,
what it will basically do is take all of
the inputs that we so neatly arranged
for it. And now it is thinking through
what to do with those inputs using the
GPT4.1 model as its brain. And then you
can see it also used the structured
output subnode there in order to give us
these scenes. So if we go to schema,
you'll see that we have three scenes in
here. And then each of the scenes has an
image prompt where we see that the
character it chose is a 22 year old man
with medium brown skin and so on and a
setting because we declared everyone to
be in a car. This person will also be in
a park car during daytime and so on. We
have a video prompt here where it
suggested this dialogue. You can
actually taste the fruity stuff in this.
It's way more than your usual beer.
Honestly, I really like it. So that
sounds pretty good. And then you have
the aspect ratios here as well as the
model. And then you have the same thing
for the different scenes here, but this
time for different characters. So you
can see this is a 28-year-old white
non-binary person with short blonde
hair. So we'll see what that looks like
in a bit. But that's perfect. We now
have all of our prompts, right? So we're
ready to feed that into our models. But
before we do that, we just need this
split out node because if we open that,
you'll notice that these scenes are
existing in N8 ends run as one item. But
if you want to generate these videos one
by one, you actually need to pass them
along one by one as well. So our end in
mind here in the output is to have three
items where we basically just split out
these scenes into their individual
items. So very simple, we just added
split out. The only thing we defined
here is which field to split out, which
is basically the scenes group. So that's
what we'll be splitting out. And then if
you execute that step, all that really
did is to output those three items where
now if you go to the table view, you
have those same image and video prompts,
but you now have one, two, and three
items there. So that's perfect because
now we can proceed to actually
generating those videos. And the way
this is done is via two steps. First,
you generate the image to put those
characters that the AI agents chose with
the product that you gave it. And then
once those images are generated, we then
pass that along to our video model which
is V3 fast in this case via an
imagetovideo request so that we sort of
animate those videos including the
dialogue that we selected. So let's do
this. If we open create image, this node
is basically called an HTTP request node
because all it really does is request a
thirdparty tool or a thirdparty model to
do some sort of job for us. Which is why
you can see we set the method as post
because you're sort of like posting a
message. And if you're posting a
message, you need an address to do that.
And so this is that address. And you can
see that we are using OpenAI's GPT40
image model, sometimes called GPD image
one. But we're doing that via this
service called key.AI, which we featured
already a lot in this channel. But if
you look at key.ai, what they are is
basically an AI model aggregator. So
think of them as sort of like an app
store that makes it really easy for you
to access these models. So you can see
there's a lot of models here and the one
we're using is this 40 image API and
this is the address to request that
from. You can see we just have our
credentials set up here. So again we
featured that in previous videos or if
you're part of the community. You can
also learn how to do that in our setup
guide in our classroom section there.
But with every request you obviously
would need the body of that request. And
so this is where we define that and we
are defining that using the JavaScript
object notation format or JSON. All we
really have here is key AI's accepted
structure for a request which we got
from their documentation. You'll see
we're passing along once again this
Google Drive link which if you open this
this is just going to point to that same
image that we gave our agent before but
obviously we also have to give it to our
chatpt image model the same way that you
would actually do it if you were in
chatgpt.com. And then we just have the
prompt here which is again a dynamic
value but you can see that we just got
this from this previous image prompt and
so that is what is showing and you can
actually cycle through this to show the
tree prompts that we're about to pass
along. Now there's some special
characters here right where we are
replacing a few things. This is just a
way in N8N to what you call escape
characters like these double quotes or
these back slashn or new lines because
to services like key it will actually
cause problems for you. So this sort of
syntax handles that for you
automatically because if you don't have
that it will say something like the JSON
structure is incorrect. So there's a lot
of sensitivity there. This is just a
required field I believe where we are
defining how many images we want and
obviously for this case we just want
one. So the last thing I set up here is
just a batching component. So what that
is basically saying is since we have
three items to pass, we'll just pass
them one by one, one item per batch in
an interval of 3,000 milliseconds. So
basically 3 seconds. And that's just a
way to not overload the request, which
sometimes results to problems with the
payload. So if we execute this step, it
will show a status of 200, which means
that our request has been accepted. It
doesn't mean that the image has been
generated yet because that does take
time which is why we have a wait node
here which if we open that we just set
this as 300 seconds or 5 minutes which
is usually more than enough time for the
images to generate. So if you execute
this step what that will just do is
countdown literally from 300 seconds to
zero. So once that is done you can now
move on to this next node which is just
a way for us to get the images that we
just generated. So it's another HTTP
request node where we are getting the
images from this URL of key AI and again
this is as per their documentation. We
just have our credential set up there
once again and the only thing that we
are passing here is the task ID which we
got coming from the create image that
was assigned to us to point to the
specific request that we just made for
it because key AI is a big place. This
one ID will just point to what image we
actually generated. So if we execute
this step, we can see if that image has
now been done. And even though this is a
status code of 200, sometimes it varies
per provider. For KAI for example, what
you actually need to look for is this
success flag. And since it says zero and
since there is no image URL anywhere
here, that basically means that it is
still generating. In fact, it says so
right here. So if it's still generating
what basically will happen here is after
this node there is this if node which is
pretty standard practice with a lot of
these creative N8N workflows where
basically what this is saying is if that
success flag is equal to one let's
proceed to the next step but since it is
not get one what will happen is if we
execute this step it will just map to
the false branch here right so what
happens there visually is that instead
of mapping to true and proceeding to
creating the videos we just mapped it
back to the wait node for us to wait a
bit more. And so whenever you run this,
it will just loop back up until all of
those images have been generated. And if
you are running through this manually,
what you can actually do is if you go to
your KAI dashboard, you can just head to
your logs section here and under 40
image, you'll be able to find the status
of those three requests. And you can see
here that they have now finished
generating. And so if we re-execute this
get image step, you'll now see that the
success flag for these three items are
now one. The status also says success.
So that is looking good. And in fact
here obviously when this workflow runs
in the background, you won't see these
URLs anymore. But if you just copy
those, you can actually preview it in
your browser tab. And that is looking
pretty good. So it's in landscape, the
guy's in a car, which is as per our
instructions with the agent earlier. And
it actually looks very realistic. And it
even got a lot of the text correct.
Obviously, it's not as perfect yet, but
honestly, if you just zoom out and later
once you see this as a video, a lot of
those will not really be noticeable. And
this is also the worst that it will ever
become because text adherence is so
important. I feel like at some point
these problems will anyway be solved.
Anyway, that is good. You now have your
three images. This is the second one.
So, that's looking good as well. And
this is the third one. So, this one's
interesting because they're not looking
at the camera. So, we'll see how V3
handles that. But, all right. Now that
that is done, we can proceed. Let me
just pin these nodes so that I don't
lose them. There you go. Because now we
are going to create the videos, right?
So this is once again we are going to
post a request. We are still using KI as
a service, but this time we'll be using
V3. Now the reason why I chose KAI for
this workflow is because as of right now
they actually offer V3 at the cheapest
possible option for you if you're doing
it on an automated manner. So they're
able to offer V3 fast at 40. If you go
to other AI model aggregators like file
AI or I think even replicate those
services actually charge a cost of $3.2
per video which is eight times versus
KAI. Google flow is actually cheaper but
two problems there is you need to
subscribe to their monthly plans whereas
KAI you can do it on a pay as you go
basis and number two I don't think they
have an API yet as of this moment. So
you'll have to go to their platform and
software and you'll have to do a lot of
the prompt engineering yourself and also
upload the images coming from chatpt
whereas here the N8 workflow as your
orchestrator handles a lot of that
automation for you and actually talks to
a lot of the models that you need. So
it's just much faster overall. Any case
that is the reason why we're using key
and you can see it's pretty much the
same here. And if you open this body
that is again just coming from KAI's
documentation where we are giving it the
prompt which you can see here again you
can shuffle through the three different
prompts that our AI agent generated for
us. The model and aspect ratio is here.
And then we have here the image URL
which if we open that that's basically
the generated image that we had from
earlier which is what we need in order
to do an image to video task. So I think
we have everything we need. We have
batching turned on as well here just for
hygiene. And now if we execute that
step, this should give us status code of
200 as well, which indicates that we
have successfully posted that request.
And once again, we are going to wait for
that generation. This one is set to 600
seconds because if you're using V3
quality, that's roughly the time it
takes. V3 fast is actually much faster.
I think 2 minutes, 3 minutes is usually
enough. So you can just change this if
you want. But if we execute this step,
it will just countd down from 600
seconds to one. same as before. And when
that node has finished and the workflow
gets to this part, all we are really
doing is to get that video. Same thing,
we're getting the record info. And same
thing, we are getting the task ID here,
which we got when we sent that request
and KI assigned us that unique ID. So if
I execute this step, it will show you
the status of each. The first one is
actually already complete, but the
second one not yet. And so we just have
this if node here functioning the same
way where we are just checking if those
have been all successful or not. And
here you can see that it sort of
bifurcated right? So you have a true
branch here where one item is already a
success and the false branch here is
basically saying that two generations
are still not yet done. So for those two
items what'll happen is it'll just go
back to the wait node while you can see
one item here is already proceeding to
the next step. So that's how it will
happen when it runs in the background.
But for our case, let's just wait for
the rest of those two videos before we
proceed. So once again, you can just
check your logs at KAI. And it seems
like those three videos are now all
good. So what we'll do next is let's
just re-execute this get video. And that
should indeed tell us that these are all
successful. And so now if we click on
this if node, all of them should be
true. So we're passing along those three
items into our final output nodes where
basically we just have this extra node
to get the video files. All this really
does is we have this method set to get.
We are passing along the URLs from the
preceding node which is this result
which again this is a link that you can
actually preview in your browser. It
ends inmpp4. So these are the videos
themselves. So we'll be viewing them
later together. And that's everything
you need for this config. We're
basically just translating those URLs
into once we execute this step actual
data which if you think about videos
they're all just data under the hood
right. So you have the three items here.
You can actually view them within N8N to
preview it. So, this is the first one.
>> You can actually taste the fruity stuff
in this. It's way more than your usual
beer. Honestly, I really like it.
>> That's pretty interesting. And then
let's view the second one.
>> I swear this has to be the fruiest beer
I've tried. Like, you actually get the
punch of citrus. It's kind of addictive.
>> So, that looks pretty good. And you can
also see some subtitling here, which is
still a problem sometimes with VO3,
unfortunately. So, as per Google,
they're working on that. But there is a
probability that you may get that. So if
I were to use that video, I'll probably
just crop that out. And then the third
one, let's see.
>> You know, when a beer actually has
flavor, this one's super fruity, like
drinking summer. I could relax here all
day.
>> That looks pretty good as well. But I
think because of the landscape nature of
it, I think that functions more like a
B-roll rather than a UGC type ad. But
with those files now loaded, you now
just have a final note. This is entirely
your choice. I just put in here box
because that is actually the easiest to
set up the credential for. N8N has a
single sign on method there. But all we
are really doing here is uploading those
files. You can see the file name. You
can decide this on your own, but we're
just setting the task ID here for it to
be unique. And then ending withmpp4
because that's the file type. We turned
on the binary file, which is basically
what you call these files that we just
loaded inn. And then the input binary
field is called data because these are
named as data. So that is quite
straightforward. If you just execute
that step, what it will now do is upload
those into our box account. This is my
box account. Let's just refresh that.
And there you go. We now have those free
landscape videos with us as well. And
there, that is the workflow in full.
Now, a few tips and thoughts as well.
The great thing about this workflow is
that you can actually feed it any image.
So, we have people in the community who
tried methods like this with furniture,
for example, and that works fairly well.
And if in case you are working with a
brand who let's say has a defined target
market, you can just go to your edit
fields node and just define that under
this special requests on what the age
range is. You can define all of that
here in your creative brief the same way
that you would brief a creative designer
for example. And then the other thing
that we were discussing in the community
is the way by which you can pitch
clients using this kind of workflow.
Because let's say you have a client in
mind in your network, what you can
actually do is just run this workflow on
their product without any permission and
just show them the output, right?
because I think we're at the stage where
a lot of business owners don't really
realize yet a lot of the capabilities
with video that we have shown here in
this channel. And so there was one
member in our community who has found
some success in that similar to if you
remember when website builders like
framer or web flow or those types of
easy web design platforms came about. It
basically enable web design creative
agencies to pitch clients by creating
the website from scratch just to show
them what the capabilities are even
before being hired. So that's one option
for you to explore which is possible now
because of the sheer low cost to make
one video which is only like 43 cents.
And if you need a breakdown of the cost,
I laid it out here very simple. It's
basically just 43 cents per video which
is magnitudes lower versus if you were
to hire an actor to do this for you. So
that would be your variable cost which
is basically the cost per video.
Obviously you have a fixed cost but if
you are already using N8N then this is
not really incremental for you but that
is just something to be aware of. And
also obviously this is for an 8-second
video. In a future lesson that I am
planning I will show how you can extend
that for UGC type videos as well. Still
all automated using N8N. So stay tuned
for that. And if you need the template
for this, which is basically like a
shortcut where you can just import it
here in N8N without having to set it up
yourself, as well as the setup guide of
how to set up all those credentials and
everything in between. You can just find
it in our classroom section if you are
part of the community. And if you're not
yet part of this group, then do check it
out to see if it's for you. A lot of
people join because of the dozens of
lessons on AI and automation here. all
geared towards helping you create better
with AI with a lot of tutorials and
lessons here around faceless videos as
well as content automation and also
creative agency work as well if you're
into that. And even though that's the
reason why people join, a lot of people
stay because of all the opportunities
for collaborations with the community as
well and also because of events that we
have with industry experts like this one
with Sabrina from BLO. So, if you're
looking for those step-by-step courses
with those ready to load automation
blueprints, including a chance to
collaborate and also earn from AI, then
have a check at the community to see if
it's for you. But that's it. Consider
liking and subscribing on YouTube
because that just helps us a lot to keep
on putting out more content and learning
tutorials here on this platform. That's
it for this one, guys. See you next
time. Thank you.
[Music]