VO3.1 Nano Banana Sora 2. There are all
of these amazing models dropping. So, I
figured why not just build a system
where we can use all of them. So, what
we're going to be looking at today is
the ultimate UGC ads system where all
you have to do is fill in some raw
information on a Google sheet like a
product photo, the ICP, the features of
that product, and a setting of the
video. And then all you have to do is
come in here and choose your model.
Whether that is V3.1, a combination of
Nano Banana and V3.1, which is super
cool. I'll show you guys exactly how we
do that in a sec here, or using Sora 2.
This lets you seamlessly test a bunch of
different creatives and product features
and settings across a ton of these
different AI video generation models.
So, the question that we're going to be
trying to answer today is which one is
best for UGC ads. So, taking a look at
this workflow, you can see that there's
basically three paths. There's the VO3.1
path, the Nano Banana Plus V3.1 path,
and then the Sora 2 path. So, we're
going to jump into a live demo. We're
going to run all three of these paths,
and I'm going to explain what every
single node is doing so that you guys
can set this up for yourself. And as
always, I'm giving away the entire
system for free. All you have to do is
join my free school community. The link
for that is down in the description. So,
before we go ahead and run the live
example, let's look at a few of our
outputs that we've already gotten with
this exact system. So, the first product
we tried was creatine gummies. Here is
what the actual product photo looks
like. So, you can see it's a creatine
gummy jar. We then have the ICP, which
is young adults wanting to stay fit. The
product features for this are delicious
gummies, easy to remember to take daily,
makes workouts better, more energetic,
stuff like that. In the video setting,
we have a young man who is parked in his
car about to go into the gym holding the
gummies. So, the first one we'll look at
is Nano Banana Plus Google V3.1.
>> I love that these creatine gummies
actually give me more energy for my sets
and they're tasty, so I actually
remember to take them every day.
>> All right, here's the same one with Sora
2.
>> I love these creatine gummies. They
actually taste amazing and I never
forget to take them. They make my
workout stronger and I feel more
energized.
>> And then here's V3.1. These taste
amazing and I actually remember them
every day for a my workouts feel
stronger and I've got more energy.
>> You may have noticed a few things with
the reference image and the way they
were speaking, but let's continue on to
the second example which was hair shine
spray. So, I'm going to go in the same
order. Nano Banana Plus VO3.1 Sor 2 and
then V3.1.
>> I love how this gives my hair that
glossy finish without any greasiness. It
dries instantly and feels weightless. I
love how this gives instant glossy shine
without any greasiness. It dries fast
and feels weightless. I love how this
adds instant gloss without feeling
greasy. It dries so fast and leaves no
sticky buildup.
>> All right, so we've seen a few examples.
We'll come back at the end and compare
more outputs and see which one we
ultimately deem being the king of these
models. But let's go ahead and do a live
example. So the first two that we did
were AI generated images. This first one
was creatine gummies, as you can see,
and the second one was our hairspray,
which looked like this. So, what we're
going to do for the third example is a
real product image, and this is actually
from an Amazon listing. So, it is a
portable neck fan like this. We have the
ICP of middle-aged adults who spend long
hours outdoors or landscapers,
construction workers. We have product
features like it's comfortable, it's
light, it delivers powerful air upward
and downward, and it regulates your body
temperature. And we have the video
setting for a friendly middle-aged woman
tending her garden in the afternoon sun.
So, hopefully you guys can see the value
prop here. it'd be really easy to just
throw in your product information right
here and then have this thing every day
create tons of UGC ad content for you.
Then what happens in the workflow is it
takes that and we have different AI
agents here that are trained to prompt
in different ways and that's how we're
optimizing you know the features and ICP
and the setting to actually go into this
UGC content. So I'm going to go ahead
and hit execute workflow. It's going to
pull in that data from the sheet. It's
going to do one row first and the first
row that it's doing is nano Banana plus
V3.1 because as you can see right here
it's basically processing this row and
that's the model that we chose was
NanoBanana plus V3.1. So I'm actually
just going to start to explain what's
going on here as this is running. So you
can see here we're pulling in data from
this sheet, right? The only thing
special going on here is we're making
sure that the status column equals ready
because we don't want to pull in all of
these rows that have already been
finished. And then we also turned on
this option that says return only the
first matching row because we don't want
to do, you know, all six of these at a
time. We want to just do one by one. You
could obviously change that if you want,
but that's the way we're rocking right
now. Anyways, we then go into this
switch node and what happens here is it
basically just checks what the model was
selected as. So if it was V3.1, it goes
up. If it was nano plus V3.1, it goes to
the middle. And if it was SOAR 2, it
goes down. As you can see, these three
paths. So, this one was obviously V3.1
plus nanobanana, which is why it went
here. And that's why we're doing this
first step, which is an image prompt.
So, let me explain why I'm doing this.
What we're starting with is a picture of
our product because we need to make sure
that the product image looks actually
good in our final copy. Otherwise, we're
not going to be able to sell any of
that. So, in my mind, the most ideal way
to do this is to take that product image
that we're given. So, if we just want to
get a quick refresher, taking this
product image right here and using AI to
turn this into an image where someone is
wearing it or holding it and then we can
take that optimized image and turn that
into a video. And so, ideally, I would
do this also for Sora. But when you send
a image to Sora, if it looks like a
realistic human person, even if it's an
AI generated human, it's going to reject
it. Google VO3.1 however does not reject
it which is why we have this little
extra bonus method here. Now the
workaround here is if you do Sora 2 you
can use cameos. So if you haven't seen
that before then I'll drop my video I
made with Nitn and Sora 2. I'll tag it
right up here and you can see you could
use cameos. So you could create one of
yourself or you could use some other
person and have them being in your
content with your product something like
that. So anyways we're using Nano Banana
to create an image of the product being
held or worn by a person. And then we
take that image and we turn it into a
video with VO3.1. So anyways, you can
see that that actually just finished up.
So that's telling me I need to speed up
a little bit. Let's click into this AI
agent to understand how it is making an
image prompt. We're giving it two
things. We're giving it the product,
which as you can see, if I open this up,
it's coming through as portable neck
fan, and we're giving it the image
setting, which is actually just the
video setting, but it says, "A friendly
middle-aged woman is tending her garden
under the sun. She pauses, smiles at the
camera, and gestures toward the sleek
fan resting around her neck." So the AI
agent takes that information and then it
reads through its system prompt to
understand what do I need to do with
that information. I'm not going to read
this entire system prompt, but you guys
will be able to once again download this
template for free and you can dive into
this and understand why I have it set up
this way. One thing I did want to
preface though is I made this workflow
to be a template. So these system
prompts are not perfect or optimized and
it would really be on you to get in here
and customize them a little bit for your
use case, but it gives us a great place
to start. So anyways, you are an expert
in hyperrealistic UGC userenerated
content photography and your role is to
generate detailed image prompts, not the
images themselves. So you will be
provided with a product photo which
should not be changed or altered in any
way. And you will also be given a
specific setting or scene description.
So it knows that its role is to create a
prompt. So we come in here and we give
it some prompt guidelines. We talk about
human realism. We talk about product
accuracy. We talk about composition and
perspective. We talk about lighting and
environment. We talk about authentic
details, technical style. And then
finally, some critical instruction like
only outputting the image prompt, not an
actual image or you know, hey, here's
your image prompt. You know, we just
want the prompt. So, out of that, what
we get is our image prompt. And you can
see it's pretty detailed. It has stuff
like lighting. It has stuff like camera
angle and composition and stuff like
that. And we're able to take that
output, feed it into the next node,
which is our HTTP request to a service
called Key AI, which lets us access tons
of different AI image and video
generation models. So this is key. As
you can see, we have tons of stuff like
VO3.1, Sora 2 Pro, 40 image, Flux
Context, Cling Turbo. It's kind of like
the open router for image and video
generation models. So, I'm not going to
deep dive into exactly how I set up this
API call, but definitely go and watch
that sore video if you haven't because I
actually go step by step and show you
guys how I did that. I'll also tag right
up here an API video that I made, which
you should watch anyways because it
really explains APIs and agents and
stuff like that. Anyways, essentially
what we're passing over here is our JSON
body, which is the most important part.
The model that we want to use is nano
bananait. We're sending over the input
prompt, which as you can see right here
is coming through. This is the output of
the image prompt agent that we just
looked at. Now, there is one thing I did
here that's kind of special is I
replaced new lines because you can see
if I get rid of this expression real
quick, what happens is we get these
little line breaks in here and we don't
want that because that will actually
break our request to key AI. So, that's
why I use that little expression. I also
talk about that in the Sora video. And
then we're giving it the image URL,
which is the one that came from our
Google sheet right here as you can see.
Finally, we're just saying we want this
to be vertical because a lot of times
the UGC content is kind of selfie style
and it's for like a Tik Tok or an
Instagram reel. So that's what we do
there. Once key gets this request, it
basically says to us, okay, cool. I got
all this information. We're working on
that right now. And so the next step
that we move into here is a wait node.
You can see that I have this set up for
5 seconds. So it goes ahead and it waits
for 5 seconds and then it checks in on
key and says, "Hey, do you have my order
done yet?" And we're able to get to that
by sending over the task ID of the
previous order. So it's like when you go
to a food truck and you order your food
and it says, "Okay, your order number
43." This is basically you walking back
up to the truck and saying, "Hey, I'm
order 43. Is it done?" And they'll
either say yes or no. And that's why we
use this little if node right here,
which is basically our yes or no check.
And we're looking to see if the state
equals success. Because if you look at
the first time we checked in, the state
equals waiting. The second time that we
checked in, the state equaled waiting.
And finally, the third time we checked
in, the state equals success, which
means that our order is ready. And so
notice that we have false branch or true
branch, and it's true when it's done. So
what we do is if it's false, we have
this line that goes back to the wait. So
this is why you can see it waited three
times, which means this took about 15
seconds to generate. And so the first
time it wasn't ready, it came back.
Second time it wasn't ready. We checked
in again. And then the third time after
it waited again, it was done. And so
when that's done, what we end up doing
is we want to real quick analyze that
image to see what is actually in there.
So here's the actual image that it
created for us, which looks awesome.
It's a green portable neck fan. She's in
her garden, and it even matches the
writing, as you can see. See, if we go
back to the source image, there's a
little bit of gold text right there.
There's these circles. So, that looks
really good. And so, I basically grabbed
this open AI note and said, "Describe
what's in the image. Describe the
environment." Stuff like that. And we
get back, the image features a woman
standing outdoors in what appears to be
a garden. The environment has raised
garden beds, blah blah blah. The woman
is wearing a light blue shirt. She has
her hair pulled back. Around her neck,
she has a green wearable device that
looks like a personal neck fan. Blah
blah blah. So, the reason why I wanted
to analyze the image real quick is
because the next step is to use another
AI agent to create a video prompt. And
in order to create a video prompt that
is consistent with our image, not only
are we going to give it that image, but
we also want to give it a quick analysis
of what is actually in that image so
that its prompt is consistent. And I
have tried doing this without the
analyze image step and it still works.
But doing this, it just seems to be
higher quality. So, anyways, we are
hitting another AI agent. This time
we're giving it a little bit more
information because keep in mind this
agent isn't just creating a video
prompt. It's also creating the dialogue
that the person in that video is going
to say. And so in order to do that, we
give it the product. We give it the
product ICP. We give it the product
features. We give the video setting. And
here's where we give it the reference
image description. So this is the
analysis of that image. So it looks at
all that information and it says, "Okay,
what do I do with that?" And so now we
have our system prompt. Once again, not
going to read the whole thing, but you
guys can have access to it for free. So,
we said that your role as an expert UGC
video creator. Your task is to generate
a prompt for an AI video model like
VO3.1. Your goal is to create a
realistic selfie style video that
appears to be filmed by an influencer
using one hand to hold the phone and the
other to interact with the product. The
video needs to feel authentic, which is
why UGC ads are converting so well right
now because it's just real people
speaking real raw thoughts. Anyways, we
gave it some requirements like subject
and framing. We talk about the visual
style. We talk about tone and dialogue.
We give it some technical specs. We give
it some embedded elements in the prompt.
As you can see, we tell it that it's
going to get a reference image and it
needs to match that appearance and tone.
And then a real quick output prompt,
which is pretty concise. And honestly,
it looks like I might have accidentally
cut off the last sentence here, but
hopefully it still came out all right.
And so after that, we get this output.
You can see it starts off with a natural
selfie style 9x6 vertical video, 8
seconds long. friendly middle-aged
woman, gardener. She's filming on her
phone. She's wearing a light blue shirt.
And then down here is where you can see
what the dialogue says. So, I love how
it's so light. I almost forget it's on,
but it pushes a ton of air and the
battery lasts all afternoon. So, that
basically took the product features that
we had given it and it made a quick
little blurb for this influencer to say
in the video. Now, we're going to take
this video prompt and we're going to
feed that into key once again and we're
going to send it to VO3.1. So, here is
our HTTP request where we're submitting
an order to VO3.1.
I'm going to open up this body, and you
can see that we have a prompt, which is
exactly what we just got from the lefth
hand side. Now, the reason it looks all
messy like this is because I'm actually
using three replace functions. I'm just
going to replace new lines, which we
already talked about. I'm going to
replace double quotes right here. It
previously said, I love how it's so
light and pushes a ton of air, and this
was wrapped in double quotes, but we
took those away because that will also
break the JSON body. And then I also had
to add another one. Sometimes based on
your chat model, it can be really weird
and output these double curly quotes
which don't actually get captured with
this previous replace function. So I
threw in this one just as an extra
guardrail which you guys will already
have all this set up. So you should be
good to go. But now we're basically
ensuring that our request will go
through. You can see once again we're
giving it the image URL except for this
one is actually the image you know it's
this one that Nano Banana made for us.
And then for the model we're saying V3
fast. We're using fast instead of
quality because it's cheaper and it's
faster and it's still really good. And I
know this says V3, but trust me, this is
using V3.1. And then aspect ratio 9x6.
We wanted to make sure that it matches
the source image. So now that we have
that, it basically does the exact same
thing. It gives us back a order number
or some sort of ticket. And we go ahead
and wait for 10 seconds right here. We
then go ahead and check back in on this
request, giving it our order number to
make to see if it's done or not. And
then you can see this happened eight
times. And so we basically checked in
eight times. So a total of 80 seconds.
So almost a minute and a half. And then
when we realize that the order is
actually done, we go ahead and we write
back to Google Sheets. And let me show
you real quick how we set up this Google
sheet right back. So we're using the
operation to update the row. And we
choose our sheet. Of course, we shoot we
choose our document. And then it says
that we have to match on a certain
column. So what we decide to do is match
on the column number. So you can see
right here, all of these rows have a
different unique number. And when the
workflow gets triggered, if we go all
the way back down to our initial get
rows, you can see that this row came in
and it was row number 10 or technically
row number 11, but the number was 10.
And so we're basically going to drag in
the number right here and say, okay, the
row that we want to update is the row
where the number column equals 10. And
so that's why it was able to write back
to this row right here, which you can
now see has been changed to status
finished. And we have our finished file
right here. because in Nitn we manually
set the status to be finished and then
we drag in the finished video URL that
we just got back from our key request.
And so that's basically the full process
and that's the most complicated one
because both the top one and the bottom
one are just doing reference image to
video rather than reference image to
image and then taking that image to
video. So anyways, we just covered the
hardest one and then we'll look at the
other ones. But real quick, let's just
go look at the actual output because of
course I'm very curious. I love how it's
so light I almost forget it's on, but it
pushes tons of air and the battery lasts
all afternoon.
>> That's really impressive. I was nervous
to see because it's different from
someone holding a product. She's
actually wearing it. But I mean, the
voice was really good. The tonality was
good. I thought that this was an
impressive result. But let's move on to
the next one, which is Sora 2. So, what
I'm going to do is go back into the
workflow and I'm going to execute it.
What this is going to do is pull in the
next And you can see it got pushed down
to Sora 2 because when it does this
check for the model, it knows that the
model was right here marked off as Sora
2. So I'm honestly not going to spend as
much time in these next two flows
because you guys pretty much already
understand exactly what's going on. We
have this video prompt agent which once
again is looking at the product, the
product ICP, the product features, and
the video setting. The only difference
here is that it doesn't have a analysis
of the reference image because it'll
just be given that. But the system
prompt once again we basically say
you're an advanced UGC video creator.
You're optimizing for video prompts for
Sora 2. Here is what you'll be given.
And we go over basically the same exact
headers. Subject and framing, visual
style, uh tone and dialogue, technical
specs, prompt, construction,
instructions, and an example output
prompt as you can see down there. So
what that does is it once again it
outputs us a video prompt. And you can
see in this one there actually are new
lines. So, good thing we have that
guardrail baked in to get rid of those
new lines. As you can see in this HTTP
request to key, we fill in our body by
saying, okay, the model we want to use
is store to image to video. Here is the
prompt. And of course, we're using all
of those nasty replace functions once
again. We've got the image URL, which
we're grabbing from the Google sheet,
which once again looks like this right
there. And we're basically just sending
all of that over. And so, it's going to
take that video prompt and it's going to
take that source image and it's going to
turn that into a video. We're doing the
exact same thing here where, you know,
we submitted the order, we have to wait
10 seconds and then check in and we're
going to go ahead and constantly be
checking until we know that our video is
done. On average, I have been seeing
that V3 fast is finishing in anywhere
from a minute to 2 minutes. And Sora 2
has been taking typically a little bit
more than that, maybe a minute and a
half to 3 minutes. There are a few
things to consider. Sometimes if you do
something like a cameo, it's going to
take longer. If you've got a really long
video prompt, it'll take longer. Also,
what can influence it is how many people
in the world are trying to use keys
endpoints. that can make it take longer,
too. But typically, Google V3 fast is
faster, but it's the exact same flow
from there. We're pulling it back in.
We're doing the same match to update the
row, and then we're just updating the
status of finished. And we are putting
in the final video link into the Google
sheet. There you go. It looks like it
just finished up. Let's go back into the
Google sheet. It just got marked as
finished. And we have our file. So,
let's take a look at the Sora 2 output.
>> Man, this thing is so light and the
airflow hits my face perfectly. Keeps me
cool while I work. And the battery lasts
for hours, so I don't have to worry
about it dying out here.
>> Man, well, that was another really good
one. A little bit confused where this
thing came from. That was a bit of a
hallucination, but as you can see, this
was the reference image, and it looks
really good in this video. Super
authentic, and it looks like she's
obviously standing there taking a selfie
video. All right, so the final one for
this example is V3.1. So, I'm going to
go ahead and zoom out a little bit, hit
execute workflow, and it should shoot it
up this top branch now. And I'm honestly
not even going to break this down
because it's the exact same thing. I
copied over basically the exact same
system prompt. I just switched out 10
seconds, which is how long the Sor
videos are, for 8 seconds for how long
the V3.1 videos are. And then I switched
out sore 2 for V3.1. But I wanted to
keep these prompts across all of these
flows as consistent as possible to kind
of limit the variability that we have in
order to truly see the power of these
models when we have as many things
consistent as we can. So, I'm just going
to let this finish up and I will check
in with you guys when we get our
finished output from V3.1. All right, so
you can see that that one just finished
up. Once again, took about 80 seconds.
Let's go ahead and make sure we got this
updated. And let's take a look at the
V3.1 output.
>> I love how light this is turning. It
actually blows enough air to keep me
cool for hours while I'm working.
>> Okay, so it's not too bad. I honestly
think that right now my my order is this
exact order that we have here, which is
Nano plus V3.1, then Sora 2, then just
V3.1. A lot of these VO ones have like
this super HDR weird orange glow looking
effect. I'm not sure if you guys had
noticed that. Here's another example of
the VO3.1. It's not it's not terrible,
but just in comparison to some of the
other ones, it definitely looks a bit
more orange. And then another thing I
noticed is this is the V3.1 example, and
I explicitly told it to not change
anything about the reference image
itself, but we can see the creatine
gummies is a jar and then in the video
it's a bag. And so it does have the same
branding and same font as you can see.
He even actually, this is funny, he's
got the logo on his hoodie, which is
honestly a nice touch, but this is a
bag. And in the source image, it was a
jar. And the other creatine ones didn't
have a bag. They had the the correct
jar, too. And I know we didn't look at
the forearm strengthener example, but
this was another one where, for example,
Nano Plus V3.1. Let me just show you
guys this one. I love that the
adjustable resistance actually makes my
grip get stronger week to week, and it's
small enough to use right at my desk.
like super good, super natural, and the
product photo looked exactly like it did
that I gave it, which looked like this,
as you can see right here. But then that
same one with VO3.1 without Nano Banana.
Once again, it looks a bit it has some
weird shadows and it looks orange.
>> I love how the adjustable resistance
actually lets me progress without extra
gear.
>> But it the product photo also once again
does not exactly match the source image.
So that's kind of like a huge no no for
me. And another thing that you guys will
notice when you send a source image and
you turn that into a video both with
V3.1 and Sora is the first frame is the
reference image. And this is that first
creatine example we looked at with sore
2. And you'll notice the very first
frame is once again the reference image.
And so when we do nanobanana plus Google
V3.1 it still does that but our
reference image is this. So it just is
able to you know pick up right from here
and it looks way more natural. So the
point being you could kind of like
automate the content creation and you
could have it auto post as well with
this branch, but I probably wouldn't
auto post Google V3 like this or sore 2
like this because of that whole first
frame, first couple milliseconds thing.
Now some people argue that it's good
because then you have a thumbnail, but
then every single thumbnail on your feed
would look the exact same and that I
think would just come across really bad.
So that's why I think right now my
favorite is honestly Nanobanana plus
V3.1.
Now I think Sora would give it a run for
its money if it allowed you to upload a
realistic photo of a human. Because if
we go back to this first example with
the portable neck fan when Nano Banana
made that image, even though this is a
fake person and an AI generated image,
if you tried to feed that into Soore 2,
it would block you because of content
restrictions. So that's why this combo
has my vote right now. But another thing
to consider, of course, is cost. So
comparing these options, I guess there
were technically three, but let's just
look at these two because V3 is in here
for both. But option one is nanobanana
plus V3 fast. When you're going through
KI, which is the one that we were on
right up here, a nano banana image is
going to cost you 2 cents. So not bad.
And an 8second V3 fast video will cost
you 30. So total cost per piece of
content with this system would be 32.
Now, for option two, if you're using
Sora 2 and you're going through KAI,
which is the cheapest I've seen it, so
definitely do that. It will cost you 15
cents for 10-second video. So, really
not bad at all. About half the cost of
VO3 fast. So, option one is roughly two
times more expensive than Sora 2. So,
the question is, is it two times higher
quality and will it result in two times
more conversions? Or maybe it's not
exactly a two times match because it's a
lot cheaper than how much money you'd
make per sale or whatever it is. But
there is a bit of a trade-off there
because you can essentially make double
the amount of short form UDC content
with SOR 2 for the same price as using
Nano Banana and V3 Fast. So anyways, I
just wanted to sort of give you guys all
the info, give you the template, show
you the system, and explain the
differences between these two models.
And of course, I'm really really bullish
on all of this because the fact of the
matter is you guys can get in here and
make these prompts better. You can play
around with different chat models if you
want. We used GPT5 Mini for all of them
as you can see here. And think about in
6 months from now, a year from now, how
much better these models will be when
Sora 4 comes out and when V4 comes out.
They're just going to get better and
better and better and cheaper and
cheaper and cheaper. Anyways, I don't
want this video to go too long, but I
did say that you guys could access this
entire template for free. So, all you
have to do is join my free school
community. The link for that will be
down in the description. There will also
be a full setup guide right over here
when you download this template. And
when you join my free school community,
this is what it will look like. You'll
just have to click on YouTube resources
or you can search for the title of this
video. And when you click on the post
associated with the video, you will have
right here the JSON file to download and
you import that into niten and any other
guides or PDFs that you need. I will
also write here similar to this post, I
will include the link to copy this
Google sheet template so that you guys
can plug everything in and have a very
minimal amount of custom configuration
and just start, you know, producing
these types of results. And if you want
to see me actually build this system
live and just kind of talk about what
I'm doing, why I'm doing it, and my
thought process, then definitely check
out my plus community. The link for this
will also be down in the description.
We've got a great community of over 200
members who are building with naden
every day, asking questions, sharing
what they're learning, helping each
other out, and a lot of these people are
building businesses with NAND right now.
We've also got a classroom section with
three full courses. We've got agent
zero, which is the foundations for
beginners. We have 10 hours to 10
seconds where you learn how to identify,
design, and build time-saving
automations. We have one person AI
agency which is for our premium members
laying the foundation to build a
scalable AI automation business. And
then here's the course I was just
talking about with projects where we
actually dive into step-by-step setups
of practical workflows that you can
actually use. Probably one of the best
ways to actually learn NN in and out. We
also have one live call per week.
They're super fun. Everyone gets on
there and we ask questions and we have
some cool conversations about the space,
the industry, all this kind of stuff.
So, I'd love to see you guys in those
live calls in the community. But that's
going to do it for today. So, if you
enjoyed this one or you learned
something new, please give it a like. It
definitely helps me out a ton. And as
always, I appreciate you guys making it
to the end of the video. I'll see you on
the next one. Thanks everyone.