AI avatars can't hold products naturally
until now. Because if you're running AI
avatars for your drop shipping or
e-commerce stores that look like this,
your ads won't convert. That's why I'm
revealing the secret in this video.
Motion mimicking. You simply record
yourself holding any product and AI
copies your exact movement onto the AI
avatar. So, we're going to be covering
everything in this video. The new AI
model that allows us to do this, the
prompts, the complete step-by-step
methods. Now, just so you guys know how
crazy this new AI model is, let me show
you a video ad that I created for the
rose teddy bear in less than 20 minutes.
>> All I thought it was just flowers at
first, but then I realized it's actually
a rose teddy, and it's so much more
thoughtful. What I love is that it
doesn't die after a few days like normal
flowers do.
>> Now, before we get into the video, guys,
there is a like goal of a,000 likes. So,
make sure you destroy the like button
because that shows me that you
appreciate these videos and you want to
see more of them. And if we hit the like
goal, I'll put a present in the pin
comment and in the description below.
So, let me start off by showing you guys
the first method where you don't need to
be filming yourself. You're just going
to simply be using full AI to do the
whole process for you. So, guys, the
first thing that I want to do is show
you the product that I'm going to be
using as the example with this new AI
model method, which is going to be the
Rose Teddy Bear. Now, this product I've
chosen because it's one of the most
recognizable products in the industry.
And number two, it's almost Valentine's
Day, so I thought it matches quite
nicely and the colors pink in the
background. So, I thought it all goes
together very nicely. Now, the other
reason why I chose this product is
because this rose teddy bear has a lot
of unique details that the AI will
struggle to recreate. So, the more
complex your product is, the harder it
is for AI to recreate. But the reason
why I chose this is to show you with
this new AI model method, it can simply
recreate these products without any
problems and keep product consistency,
which we all know that the three major
issues is product consistency, character
consistency, and the real skin tones
with AI video ads. So, at this point of
the video, guys, it would be helpful if
you have your product ready in mind, and
you take a screenshot of the product. So
what I've done guys is I've simply took
a print screen of my product like this
so that I can give it to the AI to
recreate. So you just need a simple
image of the product on a white
background like this. If you can also
take another print screen of the product
in a different angle. The more images
and angles we have of the product on a
white background, the better the results
are going to be. So now I've took a
print screen of the product on a white
background. I can now move on. So guys,
we now need to use the one tool that's
going to do everything in this video,
and that's going to be Arcads.ai. So
make sure you check them out in the link
in the description and in the pin
comment cuz you're going to get the best
deal on arcar ads.ai. So if you use my
link and the coupon code, you're going
to get the best offer at this current
time. Now arcar ads.ai will allow us to
create images, videos, and absolutely
everything. So we can stick to one tool,
which makes life a lot more effective.
So now you've created an account on
Arcar Ads. All you're going to want to
do is click new project. Rename the
project to whatever your product name
is. And then once you've done that,
you're going to see these options.
Talking actor, video, and image. We're
going to want to select this to image
first. We're going to click the filters
icon, and we're going to change it to
Nana Banana Pro 9 by6. Now, at this
current time, guys, we're not using the
new AI model that's going to make this
magical. I'm going to be explaining what
that new AI model is in a minute, but
for now, we need to get the image of our
person holding the product. So now we
need to describe the image. Now this
simple prompt I've used is an attractive
woman in her 20s holding this rose teddy
bear standing in her bedroom. So it's a
very simple prompt. The reason why I've
chose this prompt is because it's a
woman that's going to be gifted this
product. She's going to be roughly in
her 20s and she's going to be holding
this rose teddy bear in her hands
because she's been given it as a gift
and it's more likely for her to receive
this in her bedroom or on the couch in
her living room. So I understand where
she's probably going to be. the AI actor
based on what you're selling. What is
the individual going to be receiving the
product? Is it an older person? Are they
going to be sat outside? Are they going
to be sat inside? So, once you figure
that out, it should be very easy. You're
going to want to type a simple prompt
like this. Now, if you're really not
sure, give the image of the product to
chat GBT or give it the link to your
listing and say, "Describe who would
receive this product and give it an
example like mine and it will recreate
it for you." if you really don't know
how to do it. And that's simply if you
really don't know who is going to be the
person receiving the product. But in my
case, I do. So I can just give it this
prompt. And then in the bottom left,
you're going to see this image icon.
This is the reference image where we're
going to upload it. Now the reference
image that we're going to be uploading,
guys, is that simple screenshot that we
took of the product on a blank white
background. So I'm going to open that.
I'm going to change it to three
variations. So this is going to give me
three variations of the person holding
the teddy bear. And then I'm going to
click send. So guys, I've received my
three images. Now, this is the first
image of the lady holding the rose teddy
bear. Now, when you receive these
images, you need to think logically
because we're going to be using this as
the base image for every video we make.
So, the AI has to be consistent with
what it sees. So, you got to think
logically in the background. You can see
here there's like this plant that's
floating. This is going to be hard for
the AI to recreate every time. So, I'm
going to avoid this image. And I don't
like the way she's positioned in the
frame. So, I'm actually going to avoid
this image. This image here is a lot
easier because the background is easier
for the AI to recreate. So, this image
is very good and she stood in the middle
and center. So, in my opinion, based on
this image, like what she's wearing, it
should be very easy for the AI to
recreate this into a video. The third
image it made is also very good, but I
don't like the bed being scruffy in the
background, so I'm going to forget about
it. Now, those three images that you
made, if you feel like there's something
that's missing, either reprompt it or
just regenerate another three images.
Now, in my case, guys, I regenerated
some more images. And I've now got this
image here. So, this is the image I like
because she's smiling. I think the
outfit's easy to recreate. The size
portions of the teddy bear and her now
look more realistic. So, for me, this is
the image that I'm going to be using.
So, I'm going to download it in HD. Now,
the next thing that you're going to want
to do is head over to chat GBT, change
it to the 5.2 model, and then you're
going to want to upload that image we
just downloaded, and you're going to
send, I need a prompt for this image to
turn it into a Google V3 video. Another
purpose of this is to have it as a UGC
style or a POV style video of a woman
showcasing the rose teddy bear for a
natural looking advertisement to
showcase it. So, I need a prompt to give
to VO3. But by the way guys, once we hit
250 likes on this video, I will leave a
Google doc sheet with all the prompts
that I've used within this video. But do
bear in mind the prompts that I've used,
you are going to have to recreate them
to match your product cuz obviously I'm
selling a rose teddy bear. The base
prompt is fine, but you're going to have
to read certain parts like what your
product is and who your avatar is. You
can't just copy and paste them. Then you
can see here it says, "Here's the clean,
ready to go Google V3 prompt design."
Now, after that response, I reuploaded
the image again. I actually sent it a
prompt with the link of the product on
AliExpress. I then said, "Give me some
Photoshop ideas that I can turn this
into videos of the rose teddy bear. So,
for example, I'm making an
advertisement, a Tik Tok video ad. So,
what other poses can we put her in?
Maybe her sitting on the bed, maybe her
with her boyfriend. I'm not sure what we
could do." I want you to come up with
the ideas that you think would work for
an ad. Now, the reason why we're not
just going off the base question we gave
it first is because we're training the
AIGBT to understand what we're selling
and the reason why. So, the follow-up
prompt will then give us the better
result. So, now you can see here it goes
over high converting Photoshop plus
video ideas. Again, we're still training
the AI guys. So, now the last prompt
we're going to give it is I need you to
give me Google Banana Prompt to turn it
into images. And then I need you to give
me Google V3 prompts to turn those
images into a video. Now, essentially
what we're doing, guys, is we're getting
the AI to give us new Google Banana
Prompts to create new images that we
will then turn into videos. But the
reason why we have to turn them into
images first is because that's how we're
going to keep character consistency and
then product consistency. Now, this is
where we get the gold that we needed. So
you can see here now it's giving me the
prompt for the Google Banana Pro and
then underneath it is giving us our
Google VO3 which then turns it from an
image into a video. So essentially we
just need to go through all of these
prompts one by one. So what I'm going to
do guys is I'm going to take the first
one here which is sitting on the bed
cozy gift moment. So I'm literally just
going to copy this prompt. I'm going to
go back to Arcer Ads. I'm now going to
change the reference image, guys, to the
image that we just downloaded, which is
the first image. So, you can see now the
new reference image is the image that we
just had previously. And now I'm going
to paste a new prompt. And now you can
probably turn the variations down from 3
to two. And then we're going to click
send. And now, whilst we're waiting for
these images to be generated, we can go
back and actually grab the Google V3
banana prompt and we can copy it from
natural. So you don't need the first
part, you just need the natural part.
And we can paste it in here. And then
what we can do, guys, is we can change
this from image to video. And then where
it says video, we're going to go to the
right hand side and we're going to see
the model. We're going to use VO3.1.
We're going to use 9x6 and we're going
to use 1080p. And this is where we're
going to paste the prompt. So now guys,
you can see that we've got the new image
generated. So this image here is the one
that I like the most. She's looking down
at the teddy bear sat on the bed. And
you can see the background has stayed
consistent because we gave it the
reference image. Now the other image it
made is okay, but I'm not a fan of the
way she's positioned. I think this one
looks more natural. So I can download
the image. So now I've downloaded the
image. I can go to the reference option
here, add a reference image, and I can
add the new image here. And then I can
simply click send. So now that's going
to turn that image into a video. Now we
still haven't used the new AI model yet.
That's going to happen after the video
is generated and I'll explain the reason
why in the next few moments. So now you
guys can see the video has come back to
us. So let's view the video together.
So as you guys just saw there, the video
actually looks really good that V3 made.
Now, you might be wondering, why did we
get Google V3 to make a video if we're
not going to be using this as the main
model? And the reason why is because at
the beginning, I said to you, you got
two options. You can either create the
motion yourself, which is the advanced
version, or you can simply get AI to
create the motion. So, essentially what
we're doing here is we're getting Google
V3 to create the motion. And now we're
going to give it to the new AI model
called Cling 2.6 to then recreate. So
now what we're going to do guys is we're
going to download this video and then
we're going to go over to where it says
see more and then you're going to see
this new one here guys called cling 2.6
motion control. So this is the new AI
model that allows you to create any
motion and edit to any image that you
want. So now you're going to see upload
character image. This is going to be the
character image that we created with
Google banana. And then the reference
video is going to be the Google VO3 that
we've just created. So we've given it
the base image and then we're going to
give it the motion video. So this video
here is basically the motion. We're
going to get Cling 2.6 to add to the
video. And essentially Cling 2.6 is the
industryleading motion for video. So
this should create a video now where
it's going to be a lot more accurate of
the AI avatar doing that scene. Because
if you watch the Google VO3 one slowly,
you can see that you can tell it's AI
because the way she's holding the teddy
bear and bringing it to herself, it
doesn't look natural and the teddy bear
changes size. So, you can slightly tell
that it isn't real. And that is the main
issue right now with video models. There
are times you can tell it's not real
because of the motion that they do. The
motion does not look natural. And this
is where Cling 2.6 fixes that issue. And
this is where you guys have the choice
whether you want to get the AI to create
the motion like I got Google V3 to do it
or you just simply get your phone and
you record yourself with a product in
your hand or anything in your hand that
can replicate the product and you create
the emotion image. You can see that
she's sat on a bed with the teddy in her
hand. So I can now sit on a bed or a
sofa in a similar position and then
recreate the motion. So, let's pretend
this here is the teddy. I can look down
like she is and I can pretend to do this
motion, which is her bringing the teddy
to hug it. So, it's completely up to you
guys whether you get the AI to do it or
you simply get your phone and create the
motion yourself. Now, in my opinion, if
I was to say which one's better than the
other, I think sometimes the AI does
better. Sometimes if you were to do it
yourself, it's better. Now, the only
downside of you doing it yourself is it
takes a little bit more time and you
have more control. But essentially, the
reason why we're using Clink is because
it's going to improve the realism of the
motion of the image to video. So, it's
going to look more natural. And I'm
going to put a sideby-side comparison on
the screen showing you this here, which
is the Google V3 version. And you can
see here, this is the video. Then I'm
going to be showing you what the Cling
AI motion does. So you can see side by
side which one looks more realistic. And
I just want to quickly say this, if you
were to do the motion yourself, you are
going to get better results. And when I
say better results, I mean around about
30 to 40% better quality on the end
result. But if you really don't want to
be getting your phone out and doing it
yourself, then this is a better
alternative. Now, I do also want to say
that the Cling Motion does take around
about 5 to 10 minutes, sometimes more,
to create the video. But what I would
say to you guys is whilst you're waiting
for this cling video to be made, I would
move on to the next prompt. So, we're
going to go back to chat GBT. We're now
going to move on to the boyfriend POV.
So, now we're going to do this one,
guys. We're going to grab this prompt
here because there's no point you just
sitting there waiting for the video. You
might as well start getting on with the
next one. So, we're going to go back to
Archads. We're going to go to image.
We're going to upload the reference
image, which is the original image. Only
upload the original image every time. So
when you guys create the next images,
you need to make sure the reference
image is the same one at the very start.
Don't make the mistake of taking the
second image you made and using that as
the reference image. The reason why we
got to keep the reference image as this
one is because the lady is looking
directly at the camera. So the AI knows
what she looks like on both sides of her
face. So that it keeps the bedroom the
same and it keeps her face the same. If
I then go and take this image and use it
as the reference, you cannot see her
face clearly. So, the AI will change her
face, which means the character
consistency won't be there. Now, guys,
what I can do is I can change this
prompt over. I can then make sure that
we're on the right settings, which is
Google Banana 9 by6, and I can click
send. I would definitely recommend that
you guys make sure that you're doing
these alongside of each other. Don't
wait for one to finish. The quickest way
to get this done is making sure that one
Cling 2.0 motion is being made. You
carry on with the next prompts. For
example, I'm just going to work through
all of these as I'm waiting for the
cling videos. Cuz if you just wait for
the cling videos, guys, you're going to
be sat here for about an hour. So, check
this out, guys. This is the next batch
of images it made. So, you can see the
AI avatar is the same. The background's
the same. Everything's the same. You can
see she's looking at somebody as if
somebody was to gift it her. This is the
boyfriend gifting her the rose teddy
bear. But this image is better because
look, you can see that the boyfriend's
arms in it and she's receiving it. So,
this one actually looks really, really
good. So, I'm going to actually use this
image. So, I'm going to download it. I'm
then going to go over to video. I'm then
going to change it to VO 3.1 9x6. I'm
going to upload the new reference image,
which is going to be the image I just
downloaded. I'm then going to go to the
prompt POV UGC. Come back here, guys,
and click paste. And then we're going to
click send. And the thing is, whilst I'm
waiting for this video to be made, I
might as well move on to the next image
because even the Google 3.1 videos can
take a couple of minutes. So, I might as
well move on to the next image. Just
make sure that if you're doing this
quite proactive like I am, you don't get
mixed up with the prompts because if
you're going at quite a fast speed like
I am, you might accidentally mix them
up. So, guys, I've just received the
first Cling 2.6 motion video back. So,
let's go and view it together. So, you
can see the first change is the teddy
bear starts not in her hands. It starts
out of our hands and let's see it
together. I usually tell that these
motion videos are around about one time
slower than they should be. So I
actually speed these up in the editor.
But if you speed this up in the editor,
it looks a lot better. But generally you
can see that the overall realism looks a
lot better. The proportions, the motion,
the hand gestures look a lot more real.
Now again, we have to speed these videos
up later in Cap Cut and they look even
more realistic. Now, sometimes I'll be
honest with you, Google V3 does outbeat
the motion, but usually I will just redo
the motion again if I don't think it's
better, but overall I do believe that
Clling 2.6 makes better quality videos
than Google V3. Usually when Google does
better is if you don't do a good motion
videos. That's why I'm telling you guys
it's sometimes better to use your own
phone and record yourself doing the
motion because it's going to be more
realistic. This is just me taking the AI
video and giving it as a motion
reference. And I've told you guys
already that it's around about 30 to 40%
a lot worse than if you were to do it on
your phone. You can see the video is
ready. Now look what Google V3 has done.
That is made this video worse. It's
changed the product. So look at this.
It's added this weird brown thing on the
nose which the product doesn't have. So
this is where Google V3 breaks. And this
is why Cling 2.6 six is better because
when we change this into a motion video,
it won't break. But the the motion is
the most important part. Let's check
this out.
See, it's even added eyes onto the
product as well.
And the way she gives it back to him
looks unrealistic.
But either way, guys, the video is still
pretty good, but we're going to be using
it as the motion. So, I'm going to
download it. So, now I'm going to go
back to see more cling 2.6. Upload the
reference image. upload the reference
video.
And now click send. And I think this is
a great opportunity to show you guys why
Cling is better at the moment because it
won't change the product and it will
make it look more realistic when she's
giving it back to the boyfriend. Now,
whilst we're waiting for that to be
done, we actually need a speech for the
video. We're not going to be using the
voices in the video, although it does
create voices when you get them. We're
actually going to be using an 11 Labs
voice over. Now, what you're going to
want to do is go back to the GBT chat
and say, "I now need a voiceover script
for 11 Labs. This is for my video ad on
Tik Tok." It will then go over the video
ad options. I then say, "I just need a
voice over. It needs to be 30 to 45
seconds long." And then you're going to
see the different voice over options.
We've got an emotional story, boyfriend
gift, and then the casual reaction. So,
just choose the one that you believe is
the best. Once you have one that you
like, I'm going to choose this one.
You're going to want to use the V3 voice
because it has a motion which V2 doesn't
have in 11 Labs. Now, I've chose this
woman here called Adeline, I think her
name is, because she sounds like that's
what the one would look like. So, make
sure you listen to the voices and think
to yourself, would the AI character look
like they sound like that? If they do,
then that's good. Then, what you're
going to want to do is paste the prompt
in here. Make sure it's on the right
lines. And then, you're simply going to
want to click enhance. When you click
enhance, it will add the emotion to the
script. So you can see here surprised,
thoughtful, happy. Then you're going to
want to click generate. And then you can
play either one or two. See whichever
one's the best. If they're not very
good, just regenerate them or change the
voice over to another person and then
regenerate. Now I'm actually happy with
generation two. So I'm going to download
it. Now what I'm going to do now is guys
is move on to the next one. So I've got
another four more prompts to go through.
So it's going to take me around about
another 15 minutes to do these. So I'm
going to quickly do these and come back
to you. So guys, as we're waiting for
the videos to be generated on Arcar Ads,
I would recommend that you open up Cap
Cut as that's the platform we're going
to be using to edit the videos and put
them together. So come over to Cap Cut
and click create new. Go to 9x6. Then go
over to where it says upload on media
and just simply upload the footage that
you have available now. And once you've
received all the footage, just upload it
here. Now I've just received the footage
back, guys. And check this video out.
This one looks really, really good. So
you can see how natural and realistic
this looks. And again, this looks
really, really good. That's the video
that the Cling AI 2.6 made, and it looks
way better than the Google V3. And like
I said to you guys before, if you're
having issues with Cling 2.6, it's
because the motions that you're giving
it aren't very good, and it's hard for
the AI to understand. The better the
video you give it of the motion, and
again, you doing it yourself will be a
lot better, the better the video will
be. So now you guys can see I've got all
the footage back. So, I'm now going to
dump this into Cap Cut. Now, as I've
dumped this all into Cap Cut, guys, I'm
going to think logically about what
video I want first to be the hook or the
first part of the video. Now, I actually
like the second video clip that we made
more. Now, you don't need to do it in
chronological order, guys. Meaning that
whichever one the GBT gave you as prompt
one doesn't mean it needs to be number
one in the video sequence. Now, this was
prompt two, and I put it first. And the
reason why is cuz I like the way that
it's a massive dramatic video of her
holding it with a smile and then she
looks into the camera and then she shows
it the camera. So for me, I feel like
this is the strongest intro clip that I
can have. So that's why this is going to
be number one. Now what I need to do is
click on the clip, click audio, and turn
it all the way down and make sure the
fill buttons turned on because then
it'll make it fit the whole screen. Then
what we're going to do, guys, is we're
going to drag the voice over underneath.
We're going to play it with the voice
over. genuinely didn't expect this at
all. I thought it was just flowers at
first, but then I realized it.
I genuinely didn't expect
>> I'm actually going to turn the voice
over down a little bit. It's quite loud.
So, we're going to change it by - 9 dB
and play it again. Now, this is a lot
better. So, now I can think logically
about what I want clip number two to be.
>> I genuinely didn't expect this at all. I
thought it was just flowers at first,
but then I realized
>> then I'm actually going to put the
unboxing video number two because it's
her receiving the gift. I'm going to
make this fill. Going to go audio. We're
going to turn this one down and we're
going to play this one.
>> Realized it's actually
a rose teddy.
>> Okay, so now I actually want to trim
this down a little bit, guys. Or I'm
going to speed up. Actually, you know
what I'm going to do is I'm going to
speed this one up. So, we're going to go
to speed. I'm going to go up by around
about 1.5. And let's have a look at
this. Now,
>> I genuinely didn't expect this at all. I
thought it was just flowers at first,
but then I
>> I'm also going to speed this one up,
guys, by 1.5. I think all of these clips
need speeding up by 1.5 cuz they're a
little bit slow. Let's have a look
>> at first, but then I realized it's
actually a rose teddy.
>> See, that sounds really good. So, I like
to edit these clips as I'm listening to
them because then that way you get to
understand what should be placed at what
part of the video. So, I think that
looks really, really good
>> and it's so much more thoughtful.
>> So, now I want the boyfriend clip of her
with her boyfriend. So, let's see if we
can find that. So, I'm going to drag the
one with her and a boyfriend in here.
And I'm also going to speed this up,
guys, actually by two this time. So,
this one's quite a long video. So, I'm
going to go to speed. We're going to go
by two. I'm going to make sure this is
on fill. I'm also going to make sure the
audio is turned off.
>> And it's so much more thoughtful. What I
love is that it does doesn't die after a
It's so much more thoughtful.
>> I'm actually going to turn this one
down. It's a bit too quick. So, we're
going to go back to 1.5.
>> What I love is that it doesn't die after
a few days. Like,
>> and then the next one is I'm going to do
the mirror shot of her in the mirror.
Okay, that one's the bad one. So, we're
not going to use that one. Actually, we
are going to use the mirror one. We just
need to crop it because the start of the
mirror one looks bad. She's not holding
it. It looks fake. So, we're going to
crop it. So, her hands are now there.
So, her hands are on it. So, it looks
real. So, it's fine to be cropped there.
So, we can play it again
>> after a few days like normal.
>> And I'm going to turn this audio to
zero.
>> After a few days like normal flowers do,
it just sits there.
>> Okay. And you can crop it there. It
looks creepy as she's just sitting there
looking at it. So, like that's creepy.
So, we can just crop that down.
>> It just
>> And then we can play the next video. of
her on the bed with it. And we can speed
this one up definitely by 2.5 by 1.5.
And we can also turn the audio off. And
we can play it here. Oh, I need to turn
fill on. And then the last clip is her
holding it, presenting it to the camera,
which I believe is this one here. And we
can simply just speed this one up so it
matches the time of the ending, which I
think is 1.5. No, it's a little bit
less. So it' be 1.3. Okay. 1.2. Yeah,
1.2 is perfect. So, we can place it
here. Put this one on fill. Put the
audio on mute. And let's have a look.
>> Honestly, if you're looking for a gift
that actually feels meaningful and not
last minute, this is such a good idea.
>> Perfect.
>> Genuinely didn't expect this.
>> Just like that, guys. We've got the
video made and I think that looks
really, really good. Now, the only thing
that I need to do is add captions. So,
we're going to go to captions,
autogenerate, click generate. Now,
usually it messes it up because it adds
like these double captions. So, the
bottom ones you can always delete. So,
the ones at the bottom, you can always
delete these ones, guys. You don't need
them. So, now I've deleted those. That's
fine. I can then go to basics. I can
change the preset to black. Actually,
I'm going to do white. And then basics.
We're going to make this bold. I'm going
to change the font to Poppins.
I'm going to unbold it. And then I'm
going to make it slightly bigger. So,
we'll make it 12. And then I can make
this slightly bigger so it fits on one
line. And just like that, guys, I can
move the text up a little bit. And we
can play it. But before I play it, I
actually want to add music. So we're
going to go over to where it says audio.
We're going to click view all. I'm going
to click fresh.
This one, actually, funny enough,
although it's the first one I chose, it
sounds perfect for the video. It's got
like that romantic feel to it. So we're
going to drag this underneath. We're
going to quickly play it. But before I
play, I'm going to turn it down
slightly. So, let's turn it down by 10.
>> I genuinely didn't expect this at all. I
thought it was just flowers.
>> Perfect, guys. I don't need to do
anything. All I need to do now is just
blade this here. Let's put the pointer
here. Let's click on this. Click split.
Click delete. And now we can view the
whole ad. So, let's make this full
screen.
>> I genuinely didn't expect this at all. I
thought it was just flowers at first,
but then I realized it's actually a rose
teddy, and it's so much more thoughtful.
What I love is that it doesn't die after
a few days like normal flowers do. It
just sits there and reminds you of the
moment you got it. Honestly, if you're
looking for a gift that actually feels
meaningful and not last minute, this is
such a good idea. I
>> guys, I'm not going to lie, for around
about 20 minutes, that ad is so good.
And if you go on the ads library or
winning hunter to look at other
competitors, the fact that I was able to
make that in 20 minutes and it looks
better than the ads that are currently
performing well is crazy. The character
consistency is amazing. The background,
the whole scene is the same. The product
consistency is there. The AI avatar
looks real. Yes, there are a few little
bits that look a little bit unnatural,
but when you speed it up, it cleans it
out. But guys, that ad right there is
amazing. Yes, I have forgot to add a
call to action, like my brand name and
stuff, but for this instance, I've not
added my brand name. I've not added like
go and shop at soandso.com. You guys can
obviously do that if you want. And if
there's any parts that you think you
could remake or make better, simply go
back and reprompt archives to create a
different part of the video. But for me
personally, I think that video looks
very, very good. But let me know what
you guys thought of this method, the new
Clling 2.6 motion method, which allows
you guys to add any motion to any avatar
as you wish. But with that being said,
guys, don't forget to hit the like goal
and destroy the like button.