So, right here is a video of a girl
making a simple review of some pants
that she bought online. And I thought to
myself, how can I recreate the same
video, but replace her outfit with my
own product like this? Or even change up
the background like this while
preserving the same exact movements.
This way, I have a fully unique video
that I can use for my own products.
Well, in this video, I'm going to show
you how this is done by using AI motion
control.
So, you're probably wondering why would
you want to use AI motion control to
copy the same movements from other video
ads. Well, the first reason is because
we can use it to our advantage to copy
certain concepts that are proven to
work. So, for example, this is an ad
that's doing well for a brand called Oi
Rosie, and it's a simple 5-second video
of this girl doing specific movements
while she's wearing this dress. And what
we can do is use AI to copy the exact
same look of this video, replace it with
a different model who's wearing our
product, and then changing up the
background. This way, we end up with a
fully unique video that's not just
straight up copying the ad one for one,
but we're simply taking inspiration on
the motion. Not only that, we can also
spy on other competitors who are doing
extremely well, such as this men's
clothing store that's literally doing
like $10,000 per day. And what I could
do is look at all of their best
performing ads and we could take the
exact hook that they're using in their
video like this. Then take our own
product, put it on top of our own AI
model inside of their home, and we will
have our own unique version of a hook
that is proven to work from another
brand. And if you're still sleeping on
AI ads and you don't think they actually
work, here's the results of one of my
stores that I ran in Q4 that literally
did 130K off of one single AI ad. And
here's a Facebook campaign that I've
been using to test some new AI ads,
which has given me a pretty solid cost
per click of 86 cents and a nice rorowaz
of 2.17, giving this new store a net
profit of $445 in just the last week,
which I think is pretty good considering
that this is a new product test with a
new style of ads that I'm testing with
AI. And by the way, if you want to know
the best way to track your profits on
any of your Shopify stores, this app is
called True Profit, and it gives me a
clear view on a daily basis of how much
I'm paying my supplier, how much I'm
spending on Facebook ads, and how much
I'm paying in Shopify transaction fees.
You can connect all of your ad platforms
in just a click of a button. And all you
have to do is enter in the exact amount
it costs you to fulfill all of your
products on your store, and everything
will be synced automatically, so you
know exactly how much you're making or
losing every single day. This way, you
can make the proper decisions when
you're running ads for your store. If
you want to give this app a try, feel
free to use my link down below to get a
free trial. So, first things first, you
want to find some good video ads that
you can model after from a successful
brand. Because the last thing you want
to do is copy the movements from an ad
concept that's not even proven to work.
And one of the easiest ways to find a
bunch of ads with winning concepts is by
using Monana because they have a ton of
filters we can choose from to find what
we're looking for. And me personally,
I'm going to go in their Tik Tok
database because Tik Tok has a ton of
UGC content that we can model after. And
I'm just going to filter all of these
videos by United States. I'm going to
select medium engagement so I know that
there's some traction with some of these
videos. And then I'm going to type in a
keyword like OOTD which stands for
outfit of the day because these style of
videos have a really consistent motion
that's going to work very well with
motion control. Now to get the best
results it's very important that you
find videos such as this one where
there's absolutely no cuts in between
the clips because if you find a video
with a ton of different cuts, it's just
going to mess everything up and you're
not going to get good results. So this
video that we're looking at right here
is the perfect example of what I like to
look for. And from the looks of it, I
think it's really successful cuz it has
literally 4 million views. If we get a
closer look, we can see the brand that's
actually behind this video ad. And this
brand is called Mother Denim. And I'm
just going to quickly copy the URL of
this brand just cuz I want to make sure
if they're actually successful or not.
So I'm just going to plug it into the
trending shops on Mana. And here we can
see that they're doing $11,000 per day
and they're doing around 400k visitors
per month, which pretty much tells me
that they're absolutely killing it. And
I know I definitely want to copy this ad
format for my own product. And then what
I'm going to do is just simply download
this video. Then we're going to open a
new window on chat GPT. And then I'm
going to drag that video over and then
simply say extract the first frame. And
after a few seconds, we're going to have
this downloadable link, which is going
to give us the very first frame from
that video we want to copy. And the
reason I'm doing this is so that we
could take the exact same angle of that
photo, but replace it with our own
product just like this. So to make this
work, you just want to get my GPT in the
description below, which is completely
for free. And what I'm going to do is
just upload that first frame that we
just downloaded earlier. And let's
assume that this is the product that I'm
selling on my store and I want this
model to be wearing it. Then I'm simply
just going to take a screenshot of that
and then I'm also going to upload it
directly into chat GPT. And then I just
wrote out this very simple prompt where
I say create an image prompt cloning the
first image but replacing her clothes
with this dress. And after a couple of
seconds, we now have a full prompt that
we can either copy and paste into
chatbt. But me personally, I'm going to
use Google Gemini, which I think is the
best image generator out right now. So
we're going to paste in that prompt. And
then I'm going to upload the first frame
that we extracted earlier. And then I'm
also going to drag over that screenshot
of the dress that we want applied onto
that girl. And you want to make sure
that you're using the pro model so that
you can get the best results. Press
enter. And then now we wait for the
results. And after submitting that
entire prompt, we now have an image that
looks pretty much identical to the very
first frame that we extracted. And now
all we have to do from here is apply
some motion control. So now we need to
head over to a website called
cleaningai.com. I'll leave a link in the
description below. And with my link, you
can actually get some free credits so
that you can generate your first few
clips for free. But I would strongly
recommend going with a paid plan which
starts at like $7 which is way cheaper
than what you'll ever find from pretty
much any other tool that will help you
make ads with AI. Once you're inside the
platform on the lefth hand side, make
sure you're on the AI video generator.
Then go up here and find that tab that
says motion control. And on this left
box is where we want to upload this
original video ad that we found off of
Mana. And once that is uploaded, we then
want to upload this image of the girl
wearing our product. And by the way, if
you want to know how to remove this
watermark from Gemini, just upload that
photo directly into canva.com and then
use their magic erasing tool so that you
could just brush over that watermark.
Click erase and now the watermark is
gone. And now that we have our source
video uploaded and we have the image of
the girl who's wearing our product,
that's pretty much all we need to do
from here. You don't need to enter in
any type of prompt as I don't really see
any differences in results when I do
that. And I also recommend checking this
box that says character orientation
matches video. And then down here, we
have the ability to select different
qualities. I would just recommend
sticking with 720p so that you can
conserve your credits. Only select one
output and you can choose whether you
want to preserve the same audio from
your source clip or not. And here's the
results of how this clip came out. And
you can see that it looks insanely
realistic and it's pretty insane how
it's copying the exact same movements
and still preserving this mirror very
accurately just like in the original
video. Now, keep in mind that this is
just an example and I would never
recommend running an ad using the exact
same background as your source footage.
And we can simply use Gemini to change
the background like this. This way we
have a fully unique video ad with our
own actor in their own home.
>> Outfit of the day today wearing my
favorite white dress. It's the most
comfortable dress and also flattering.
Love how it's kind of belted here and
then flares at the bottom.
>> And the possibilities are pretty endless
because you could put your actor in
whatever setting that you want, such as
outer space or even in the middle of
Antarctica. So, as you can see, it's not
really hard to do. And now I'm going to
show you just a couple of more use cases
on how you can use this for your
advantage. So, let's say I'm selling
these pair of jeans on my store and I
want to copy an ad with a proven format
while wearing these jeans. I could just
go back into Mana, filter all of these
Facebook ads by videos only, and I want
to make sure that all of these ads are
still active. And then to narrow it down
further so I can find what I actually
want, I'm going to type in pants. This
way, I have access and inspiration of
all the ads that are advertising a pair
of pants. And for example, let's just
take a look at this ad and see what
she's doing. So, you can see it's really
simple. This girl is just backing up and
then showing the features of the pants.
But let's just assume that this was
actually an ad concept that was working
extremely well. Let me show you how we
can easily recreate this using motion
control. So once again, I'm just going
to download this video clip. Then we're
going to take it over to Chat GBT. Then
I'm going to tell it to extract the very
first frame. And here's how that photo
turned out. And then just like before, I
just uploaded that first frame and then
a picture of the jeans that I'm selling.
And then I simply said to clone the
image and replace her pants with those
jeans. And then it gave me the full
prompt once again. However, I added a
slight twist where I wanted to change
the way the actor looks while still
preserving the exact same pose. And then
it ended up giving me this exact prompt
right here. And then after putting that
prompt into Gemini, this is the exact
result that I was able to get, which
looks really spot-on. And then I just
uploaded the base clip like I did
before. Uploaded that image of that
blonde girl wearing the jeans. And
here's how the video looks like after
swapping out the background. This way we
have a fully unique video with our own
model, our own product, and using the
motion as inspiration. Now, the only
slight issue is that this girl is
talking and it's going to use the audio
from the original footage, which is not
going to look right. So, the only
solution would be to use something like
11 Labs to generate our own voice and
then use a tool like sync.so to sync
that new voice on top of her lips. This
way, we can actually run it as an ad.
>> If you're done sacrificing comfort toear
denim, these are the perfect jeans.
>> But if you don't want to do all of that,
this is still going to be very useful as
we can use a lot of these scenes as
B-roll shots for any type of video ad
that we create. Another cool thing that
you could do is that you can generate
three different clips of the same exact
motion but the model wearing different
colors of your product. And if you piece
it all together using Cap Cut, you can
end up with a dynamic looking ad that
looks something like this.
Again, this was just a quick tutorial to
give you an idea of what is actually
possible with AI motion control and how
you can use tools like Mana to find a
lot of ads with proven concepts that you
can model after with your own products.
Once again, the link will be down below
in case you want to give Bana a try. And
you can also use my code to get 20% off
your first 3 months. And if you did find
this video helpful, be sure to drop a
like and subscribe to this channel as
I'm going to continue to make more
tutorials about AI and how I make ads
for e-commerce. And also follow me on
Twitter as I share tips and strategies
from time to time on everything that I'm
doing with my stores and with AI. And
with all that being said, I thank you so
much for watching and I'll catch you on
the next one.