I tested 500 meta ads using AI and
almost every single one of them failed.
Only five hook formulas kept winning
across niches, across products, and
across every creative style I threw at
them. And you can create them with AI in
under 5 minutes. No fancy camera needed,
no hiring editors, and definitely no
more paying thousands of dollars to UGC
influencers. These hooks work in any
niche. And if your ads aren't
converting, it's probably because you're
not using one of these five. And I've
spent over $1 million on meta ads for
clients in the ecom and software space.
And my top performing campaign right now
uses hook number five and has a rorowaz
of over 11x. That means for every $1 I
put in, I get 11 out. So, if you want
those same results for your campaigns,
then make sure to stick around to the
end for that one. But for now, let's get
into hook number one. Hook number one.
My problem was bad situation. Product
literally saved me. Out of the 500 hooks
I tested, this first one showed up the
most across ads, but most successful
brands don't even realize they're using
it. This is the fastest scroll stopper
you can build with AI. So, let me show
you why it works and when to use it. The
word literally makes it feel real and
emotional. You're leading with pain and
that stops the scroll immediately. And
this works for any product that solves a
clear problem. Let me give you some
examples. My skin was flaking nonstop.
Caravee literally saved me. My back pain
was killing me. This corrector literally
saved me. I couldn't hit my protein
goals. These bars literally saved me.
Now, look how easy this is to create.
I'm just going to upload an avatar here.
Type in the script and click generate.
That's it. This literally takes 2
minutes from start to finish.
>> My skin was flaking non-stop. Caravee
literally saved me. Now my skin's
actually smooth and hydrated. Best
switch I ever made.
>> Here's a pro tip. Don't just make one
version of this. Test three to four ways
to describe the same problem. Same hook
structure, but different pain language.
So instead of my skin was flaking, try
my skin was peeling, cracking. Same
problem, different emotional trigger.
And this hook works for almost anything
that solves a clear problem. Skincare,
supplements, fitness products,
productivity tools. If it fixes
something painful, this hook will crush.
And hook number one works insanely well.
But there is one problem with it. If
your audience is even slightly
skeptical, it falls apart. That's why
hook number two exists. And honestly,
this one surprised me the most in the
data. Hook number two, I've never tried
product before, believe it or not. And
this hook completely removes all the
sales pressure. When you say, "I've
never tried this before." It feels real.
It feels unbiased. And that believe it
or not part creates the curiosity gap.
And that's what keeps people watching
because they want to know what happens
next. This is perfect for trendy
products that everyone's already talking
about. Things like Prime, new gadgets,
viral skin care products, and it works
great for impulse purchases. Here are
some examples. I've never tried Prime.
Believe it or not, I'm impressed. Never
used a scalp massager. Believe it or
not, this works. I've never tried red
light therapy. Believe it or not, my
skin looks different. Now, let me show
you how to build one. So, I'm doing the
same thing, uploading my avatar and
adding the script. But here's what's
important with this hook. The avatar
needs to look curious at first and then
genuinely surprise. That is what sells
it.
>> I've never tried Prime, believe it or
not. I'm impressed.
It keeps me locked in without slowing
down.
>> And the facial expression matters more
than in Hook One because the whole point
is completely removing that salesy
feeling. If your avatar looks too
excited at the start, people won't
believe the I never tried this part. So
that is hook number two. You're
basically disarming the skepticism
before they can even have it. And those
first two hooks are all about you
talking directly to the viewer. But this
next one completely flips it around and
it crushed in niches where trust is low
and the product feels too good to be
true. Hook number three, my person has
only been using this for time frame.
This is pure social proof and it's so
powerful. Here's the structure. My
person has only been using it for time
frame. You're referencing someone else
which gives you third party credibility.
The only bean plus a short time frame
creates a sense of urgency and make the
results look fast. And this absolutely
crushes for skininc care, fitness
products and supplements. The key here
is the short time frame. Make the
results feel possible and achievable.
Not some 6 month transformation, but
something they can see in days or weeks.
Examples. My boyfriend's been wearing
this cologne for 2 weeks. I'm obsessed.
My mom's used this serum for 3 days. Her
skin's already looking better. My
friend's been taking this for a month.
His energy is insane. So, one avatar is
talking about another person's
experience. Super easy to script and it
works so well because it feels like a
real recommendation from a friend and
not an ad. Same process here. Avatar,
script, generate. Notice how this
removes another layer of sales
resistance.
>> My boyfriend's been wearing this cologne
for 2 weeks. I'm obsessed. Can't stop
complimenting him about it. buying him
backup bottles.
>> You're not even talking about your own
results. You're sharing someone else's
transformation, which makes it feel more
genuine. Now, hook three works because
of credibility. But hook four works
because of shock factor. And if you're
running any sort of visual product, this
is an absolute gamecher. All right, hook
number four. What if I told you bold
promise? Well, you're looking at it
right now. This is a patent interrupt
combined with instant visual proof. This
hook makes a bold claim and then
immediately backs it up with proof. And
this works great for products with
visible results. Think skin care,
fitness transformations, hair growth,
anything where you can really see the
difference. But here's the thing,
confidence in delivery is everything
with this hook. If the voice sounds
unsure or hesitant, this hook dies. You
need that conviction. Here's some
examples. What if I told you you'll
never have dry skin again? You're
looking at the answer right now. What if
I told you you can lose 10 lbs in 2
weeks? You're looking at that right now.
What if I told you this erases dark
circles in 5 days? You're looking at it
right now. And this is where AI gives
you a massive advantage. You can
generate the avatar that exactly matches
the promise. Clear skin. Generate an
avatar with clear skin. Fitness
transformation. Generate someone that
looks fit and healthy. What if I told
you you can lose 10 lbs in 2 weeks.
You're looking at it right now. Same
pants, different fit. Zero crash diet.
Instead of endlessly searching for the
right human creator that actually has
those results, you can just create them.
And that is the power here. And then
there's hook five, the most emotional,
the highest converting, and the one that
almost no one uses properly. This one
didn't just perform month after month.
It changed my entire approach to making
content. This one's pure storytelling.
Struggle, failure, redemption. Here's
the structure. I tried everything. List
specific failures. Then I found product.
And here's why this one converts so
well. Listing what didn't work builds
empathy with your audience. They've
probably already tried those same
things. So, you're eliminating
objections before they even happen. This
is the highest converting hook for
problemaware audiences. People that
already know they have a problem and
have been actively searching for the
solution and it is perfect for high
ticket products and transformation
offers. Examples: I tried drugstore
moisturizers, expensive serums, nothing
worked. Then I found Caravee. I tried
keto, fasting, counting calories.
Nothing stuck. Then I found this. I
tried stretching, chiropractors, heating
pads. Nothing touched my back pain. Then
I found this. Now, there's something
critical with this hook. The failures
you list must be things your audience
has actually tried.
>> I tried drugstore moisturizers,
expensive serums, nothing worked. Then I
found Caravee. My skin cleared up in
days. If you're selling skin care and
you list acupuncture, meditation, yoga
as failures, nobody's going to relate to
that. Those aren't typical skin care
solutions. You need to list the obvious
solutions in your specific space that
don't work. For skin care, that's
drugstore products, expensive serums,
dermatologist visits. For weight loss,
that's diets, gym memberships, and meal
plans. The more specific and relatable
your failure list is, the better it will
perform. And this hook also needs
emotional range in the delivery. You
start frustrated and defeated and then
shift to relief and hope when you
mention the product. That emotional
journey is what makes people pay
attention. So those are the five hooks.
And these aren't just random formulas
that I've made up. These hooks drive
millions in ad spend return and you can
recreate them with AI in just a few
minutes. Those five formulas are
crushing it right now in every niche
I've tested. And this is still early.
Only a few brands have figured this out.
Which means that right now you can test
50 hook variations whilst your
competitors are still paying creators
$500 and waiting days for the video to
be finished. If you want to get ahead
before everyone else catches on, click
the first link in the description.
You'll create your first AI UGC ad in
under 5 minutes using one of these five
hooks. By tomorrow, you could have 20 ad
variants tested and running. And if you
want the full walkthrough on how to
create AI UGC videos from start to
finish, then watch this video right