In this video, I want to show you how to
do programmatic creative testing at
scale. But first, let's figure out what
it is exactly. See, an ad, it's not only
um a piece of written copy or a nice
picture. It's you can segment an ad into
different predefined parameters. You can
have a unique selling proposition you
want this specific ad to push. You can
have the marketing angle related to this
specific unique selling proposition that
you want the ad to push. You can have a
specific messaging framework you want to
use in your ad. You can use the
awareness of your prospect related to
your product or the sophistication of
your market or even the length of the
copy. So, as you can see, there are so
many different variables that we can use
to create an ad. And by an ad, I mean a
hook or a longer copy that you can use
as a mini VSSL or whatever the ad is.
You always can segment it into different
variables. So now that AI can handle the
creative part, if we are able to build a
system to feed the right variables to an
LLM model, an AI, then the AI can
actually output the ads that we want.
Exactly. Which allow us to then generate
hundreds or thousands of different ads,
review them to make sure that they are
good. So that's the human touch. and
then push them right away into an ad
account. So we are able to literally
test with a proper structure and test
every potential marketing angle and
every potential combination that we
want. And in this video I'm going to
show you you can see two screens. Why is
because here it's the thinking process
behind it. So that's the most important
thing in this video is actually to
understand like how to think of
programmatic creative testing. Uh and at
the same time I'm going to show you the
system that I used I built for my
clients that they are currently using to
scale their ad accounts and find winning
ads after winning ads. Um and we will go
and we will see the different uh pieces
of the system one after the other. So
you will not only see a spreadsheet but
you will see a proper uh mental
framework that you can use. So who is it
for? Basically every company that is
running ads on Facebook can use this
system, this approach. If you are a
business owner, uh this might completely
change the way you think of running your
paid acquisition. If you are a marketer,
I think you will love it. And if you are
not yet at the scale of u scaling ads or
even running ads then it is worth keep
watching because what you will learn the
way to think of ads in a logical and
structural way will probably reframe uh
your approach uh so you will be a lot
better of when you you get into it. So
if you're new here my name is Steph
France. I'm a marketer and independent
consultant and on this channel I help
you to generate more revenue by writing
marketing copy that resonates with your
customer and I do it using AI of course
uh market research a lot and system
thinking before everything. So let's
dive into it. Just for context, the
system you're going to see in this video
is the exact reproduction of the system
I use for my client, but I did it for
the brand John Road Beauty, which is a
D2C brand that a lot of people know. Uh,
and I used this product as an example.
So, this way I get to show it to you
without having to hide anything. And
again this system works for every type
of product uh whether it's e-commerce uh
consumer app SAS service whatever as
long as you can advertise on Facebook
but just for the sake of the example
remember that everything you will see is
for Jones beauty a D2C brand okay so
before showing you the actual system I
want to show you the mental framework um
so you understand how it works before
seeing it and I think it's the best way
because it's kind of a complex system to
to explain and I want it to be as simple
as possible so you you grab the main
idea not the the nitty-gritty of how it
works. So let's move on first to uh this
mental framework and then after that I
will show you the different pieces but
then every time I will show you a piece
you will know exactly what it means
within this framework. So when we talk
about um programmatic creative testing,
first of all we need to generate the
ads. And to generate the ads, what we
need is the full context about the
product. And to get the full context, we
need to give as much information as
possible to the AI we are going to use.
And for that we want the AI to
understand the brand. So we want a
proper brand description. We want the AI
to understand the product that we are
selling because it's always product by
product. Uh because you can't just
advertise a brand. You want to advertise
a product of course. And then we want to
give AI the voice of the customer. And
this one is probably the most important
because the ads that we are going to
create are going to be created with
using as much as possible the proper
wording that the customers are using
whether whether it's uh in the customer
reviews or if it's on forums or Reddit
uh wherever the customer is talking
about their pain we are going to gather
all this information and we feed it to
AI every time we generate new uh copy.
So that gives us the full context about
the product then from that we are using
AI or not to generate different unique
selling proposition. What are selling
proposition? Before you ask let's read a
short description so we are all aligned.
So a unique selling proposition USP is
your product's overall unique position
in the marketplace. The fundamental
promise that differentiates you from all
competitors. It's the big picture
identity that establishes what makes
your product uniquely valuable and why
customers should choose you over
alternatives. So this is basically you
don't have many unique thing
proposition. It's like one two three
four maximum. It's like the very thing
that you you that matter to your
customer and that differentiate you from
your competitors. So once we have all
the context uh then we can think of what
are our USPS and for each USP you have
different ways to talk about it that
where that's where we use marketing
angles and as you can see marketing
angles are related to a specific USB. So
the the overall thing is like you have
your product which you have different uh
unique selling propositions that each
have
a lot an infinity of marketing angles
that we can use to talk about this
specific USP. And again quick definition
of a marketing angle it's a specific
slice or focus of your USP that becomes
the hero of one individual ad campaign.
While your USP is the strategic
foundation that defines your overall
unique market position, a marketing
angle takes one specific aspect of that
USP and makes it the central message for
testing purposes. Each angle should be
laser focused on a single emotional
trigger, customer problem or benefit.
Testing one specific way to communicate
positioning rather than trying to
communicate everything at once.
I hope it's clear. Sorry for my reading
in English that is not the best but I
get I guess you understood. So once we
have this uh
we need to frame the message that we are
going to create and we can use specific
framework that we know work. So when we
want to push a specific unique selling
proposition using a specific angle then
now we can use a specific uh messaging
framework. I will show that uh a little
bit later in the video um and it will
become more clear but let's move on.
Then we need to define
what type of uh where where is the
customer at in their journey of becoming
a buyer. So this is the level of
awareness something that uh was
introduced by Eugene Schwartz which is a
very well-known copyriter that wrote
breakthrough advertising like every
copyriter out there know about that uh
but to talk about it quickly um you have
a market that is potentially buying your
product and depending of the product you
will have
the market will be segmented in
different aspect. So for example, if
something is uh is pretty niche, then
probably the people that are aware of
the solutions and aware of the problem
are a lot uh less than if we talk for
example like John Johns Rob Beauty
skincare is very well known. So we have
a lot of people that are solution aware
problem aware. Um, if you go from the
very beginning, unaware means, I don't
even know I have the problem. Problem
aware, I'm aware I have this problem,
but I I don't even know if there are
solutions. Solution aware is like, okay,
I I've heard about the solutions, didn't
really dig into it yet, but I'm I'm kind
of aware that I have a problem and
solutions exist. Product aware is
someone that already has uh dug into the
finding solutions and know a little bit
of the market. uh and most aware would
be the people that are aware about your
specific product. So it's always like a
very specific uh pieces of the market.
But when you create again when I I go
back here, we can push a unique selling
proposition uh you using a specific
marketing angle with whatever messaging
framework we want. But we we are not
going to talk about it the same way if
we talk about uh if we talk to someone
that is just aware that they have a
problem or if we talk to someone that is
already uh very far along very far into
the journey of uh finding a solution for
this problem. So this is important to
give AI the information about who we are
talking to.
So with that said um we generate our
hooks because for the sake of this
example we are generating hooks. We
generate a bunch of them. We pick the
ones we like and then we generate an
image because we are the best way to
test a lot of ads at scale is to to use
static ads. Um video ads uh longer ads
are more complicated to produce and
static ads work really well. So we use a
combination of a hook based uh put on
different images uh that we are going to
push to the ad account uh and let
Facebook do its magic because the way we
are going to uh use uh to structure the
campaign on Facebook ads is by letting
the algorithm uh as much freedom as
possible. So Facebook will decide which
ads are resonating the most with your
customer.
So with that approach already uh you can
take it away. I'm not saying you should
stop the video, right? But just just
starting thinking about uh creating ads
in that way
is is already helpful because the the
one of the biggest problem of uh and
actually a lot of
marketing agencies uh don't have like a
structured way to to think of ads. So,
it's more creative. But again, um I'm
not I'm not a creative person. Uh I like
systems and I like to understand what
I'm doing. And if you start thinking of
ads into in something that is not chaos,
it's it's logical. It's like when you
find uh everything that you see um in
pink right here, it's like after you've
tested so many of them, you know, after
you have
this, then you find the ones that are
actually uh resonating with your
customers and and they already exist.
You just have to find them. You just
have to find the right message, the the
right framework to speak to your
customer. And then once you have them
then you can one uh scale them as much
as you can and two you can iterate from
it to create better ads.
But now let's go back into the system.
So it will be a little bit more uh
technical. But uh now I want to show you
how you can actually uh automate all of
that. If you are an established business
and you would like to uh install this
system uh then I will put a link in the
description probably a quick form that
you can just uh fill out and so I will
be notified and I will get back to you
as soon as possible. So first of all uh
brand description that's the we are
talking about the context. Now here is a
spreadsheet as you recognized it's u
it's in it's built within Google sheets
and one spreadsheet can be used for um
one product basically and every of these
spreadsheets will be connected to a back
end which is built uh within make.com
and it contains few uh automations
that are not that complicated uh but
just to show you and this is not a video
about making automations
But those automations are gathering all
the data that we put within the
spreadsheet. So you can see brand
description, product description. It
gathers everything together and and in
the end it creates those huge prompts
that we are going to use either with
cloud or with uh chat GPT and put back
into the spreadsheet. So again the point
here is not to show you automations is
that you understand that this framework
this system uh is built into a
spreadsheet which is extremely simple
but every action that we do is run on
the back end uh through make.com
connected to the different APIs AIS that
we need to make it run. So let's go back
to the brand description here. we need
to input the the information that the
brand uh that we have about the brand.
So if you don't know anything about the
brand for example if it's not yours but
a client's brand then you can use uh
prompt. So we use predefined prompt uh
to have AI dig into the brand and uh
understand all the specificity of the
branding. Then you copy it and past it
into the right section. So the system
will take all that information and bring
it to the uh um the AI on the back end.
And I actually think that I showed you a
wrong one because that was the product
but it doesn't matter because this is
the exact same approach. Then you take
the product page and you feed AI with it
which uh will give you all the
information about specific product. So
the II know what exactly uh is the
product that it's advertising and then
now we have the gold nuggets and that is
the most uh interesting and important
thing. So either the the brand the
product already has customer reviews
then we would gather everything like um
take a huge piece of copy and pasted
text of the reviews give it to AI with
predefined prompt that will only keep
the the important quotes and then we
just copy them here the same way we have
done for brand and product description
but we also want to understand what
people are talking about on the internet
and for that I'm going to link in the
the description a video that is all
about the voice mining framework. So how
to to use all the available AI agents to
gather every sources on the internet and
create this kind of gold nuggets that
are basically uh here you have the
context about a specific painoint and
then you have all the different quotes
that people um have said things that
people have said on the internet about
this specific paint and it's not
obviously related to your product, but
this is related to your pain point. So
again, link in the description, there is
a full video about it and it teaches it
shows you how to really go from you have
no idea about what to um about marketing
at all to doing all the research prompt
after prompt after prompt using all the
AI agents and end up with a master
prompt that you can use for your
marketing. market research is only a
part of it that you can you can use it
for this specific purpose but otherwise
the the video will also show you how to
just generate marketing without even
using this system. So really encourage
you to to watch it. Anyway that was
apparent uh so now we have here we have
the run description product description
voice banning so we have all the context
and now we have we want to have the
unique selling proposition. So here are
the unique selling proposition which
have been uh if you ask uh a brand like
John Road beauty they obviously know
their unique selling proposition. You
don't need AI to actually generate it
for you. But in case you need it then
you still can ask AI saying hey this is
my uh brand description product
description uh this is what people say
about our products about their programs.
please generate uh
one, two, three, five USBs for this
specific product for me and then you
input them in the system. Then here is
the first um aspect of the system is
that we can generate different marketing
angles for a specific USB which means
this is where the creativity comes up.
At this point you have for example we
are talking about this product right
miracle bomb. I realized afterward I
shouldn't have taken a skincare product
because I'm absolutely not an expert in
there in that but it doesn't matter.
This product miracle bomb the one USB
could be the only makeup that's
literally impossible to overdo and it
describes this specific USB. And now
when I generate uh marketing angles
here. So I will show you just for the
sake of showing you. I'm just clicking
here. When I click here, it triggers a
web hook. Technical thing. You don't
have to know that. But basically it
triggers one of the uh the automations
that I showed you on the back end that
is now uh generating the uh new
marketing angles for this specific USB.
So there we have them, all the marketing
angles that I've generated so far. And
as you can see, they're all related to
one specific USB. So for the USB we were
talking about, the only makeup that's
literally impossible to overdo, you can
say you can keep applying and it never
looks overdone. or if you go too strong
with other makeups, it soften back
softens it back to natural
or uh even in bad lighting or with shaky
hands, you still can't mess it up. And
then it also explains like this specific
marketing angle that is specifically
talking about this unique selling
proposition. I hope I'm not losing you
here. Um but it's very important
concept. It's what I was showing here on
the side. uh unique selling proposition
different marketing angles. So now that
we have them, let's see if we have
generated them. Not yet already, but it
doesn't matter. We don't need them. Uh
we arrive at the most important piece of
the system is where we are generating
the hooks. And as you can see here on
the left, I can pick the unique selling
proposition I want. And then I can pick
the marketing. So let's say this one
even in bad lighting or with shaky hands
you still can't mess it up and then I
have all the messaging frameworks that I
was talking about those messaging
framework they are
on the back end I'm not showing it to
you but there there are like specific
spreadsheet that uh has hundreds of
hooks performing hooks uh that are going
to be given to the AI at the moment of
generating the hooks uh as examples of
what is working in advertising basically
and for each of them we have examples uh
so you basically say okay I want um for
this one I want I don't know desire
future states
and I want to talk about just program
aware people uh the sophistication of
the market I am okay let me quickly talk
about the sophistication of the market
it's another concept that comes from
Eugene Schwarz uh in the book
Breakthrough Advertising
But I think one of the cool thing I know
uh
I realized about explaining that concept
is while I was watching a series um
quite recently I think it's 1923
uh and so in the in the US um few like
100 years ago and you see the first
people uh coming into the different
cities and selling washing machines,
laundry machines
And it struck me because they are just
showing like hey this washes your
clothes and everybody is is amazed by
that. It's like what what do you mean
it's washing my closes?
It doesn't need me to do anything. No no
it's just washing washing your closes.
And at this point the market was at the
first level. it. You didn't need to say,
"Hey, uh, this has like the it takes
your clothes and it dedicate closes and
it has all those super programs and it
doesn't, uh, use too much water and not
use too much energy and no, it was just
like, hey, it just washes your clothes.
First level of sophistication. Today for
washing machines, we are at the fifth
level, which everybody knows about
washing machines. So the only way to
actually uh
be seen by a customer is by providing
something that is different that is
different from all the other competitors
that this specific customer want. It
kind of slightly differentiate the way
we talk. So for example here uh it's
skincare uh it's fourth level, fifth
level. Maybe if the product would be
like very innovative then we could say
okay that's third level. So, I don't
know. I I can't come up with creative
stuff, but I think you you know what I
mean.
You you don't have to use it, but it's
also a way to kind of uh changes
slightly the the message that you are
using. So, let's say third level or
fourth level and we are going to use um
punchy and we want u ch5
to use it. And then to create it what we
do is basically
we are going to drag that down
and change one variable if we want. We
can also just trying to try to create
that. But we can also say okay uh now I
don't want uh only this specific
messaging framework but I want to
generate
uh bold statements
here
and I want it I want the bold statements
to be actually standard. So this at this
point is for you or your team to think
of okay what are we testing in which
order and to generate uh one after the
other basically
and then let's uh put generate click
here which will trigger the web hook on
the back end which will uh actually
generate the different hooks and now you
can see it's generating so we can go
back uh in a few minutes and we will
have the hooks here. Okay, so there we
have it. Um, it has it it took like one
minute and uh at the same time I was
just looking into the other hooks and
try to find some interesting just to
show you. But those are the ones that
have been generated just now. Uh there
are some interesting uh beautiful even
when applied blind. Shaky hands steady
glows. Steady glow. So those are punchy.
Uh standard no mirror no problem.
Miracle bombs makes mistake impossible
and glow inevitable. So that might not
be the the best ever hooks, the ever
written hooks, but they are pretty good.
And when you start having a long list
because believe me, you can have you can
generate a bunch of them and you go
through them. Now that's the moment
where you need someone that is that
knows the product human being that is
good at understanding how the the
customer and that says okay this
resonates this not this resonate this
not and then you select it's not AI
testing thousands and thousands of ads
without control it's like it generates
something and then you can select you
can even uh change it if you want but
then before generating the ads you are
going to have a human looking into
But okay uh let's say now we want to
create those ones. uh so I am just
creating generate and here I am going to
check the templates that I've created
and those templates I have created them
within this tool uh templated which
basically is a tool that you can access
through an API a little bit complicated
but you probably know what it is um that
allows to take an image and to generate
let me show you so I took a picture from
transport beauty. Here I hide the the
existing hook and here instead I put a
text and this text is just a sample here
but it will be replaced by every hook
that I'm using here. So we will have the
same picture but then it will be
replaced by that. So if I look at here,
uh it also handle the size of the the
font depending on the size of the uh the
actual hook. It's auto fit here and it
will fill the hat uh which will be uh
important for us because this one for
example is long but we are going to have
like shorter hooks and this is what
works in the back end that we can get.
Uh here we create the templates and we
decide to use um one or other another
template. But basically you have you can
have a creative team or you can go ahead
and create a bunch of different
templates of ads that you know will work
and apply the hooks that you generate on
those templates. So now let's just
create them. So we have a long one and
two short ones. Let's go
and we move on to add creation. Here
they are.
And as you can see here,
shaking hand. And it looks fresh, not
fake.
And it creates. So why it creates two
six while I had three hooks I wanted to
create simply because I activated two
templates. So for each hook, it will
create two variations.
Uh let me show you a longer one here.
For example,
no mirror, no problem. Miracle bombs
makes mistake impossible and glow
inevitable. Awesome. That's exactly what
we want.
All right. And now we are we are in this
ad creation part of the system and we
can simply move on and create the ads.
So let's say I want to create first of
all I need to select the different the
adset I want to put those ads in. So I
need to first create the campaign and
then create the different adsets. It's
it's possible to create the adsets
automatically but we ended up realizing
that it was a lot better to give the
freedom to create the structure of the
campaign and only push the ads within
the adset that have been created
already. So for the sake of this example
I create adset one. So again there is an
automation that basically retrive the
adset that are existing in a specific
campaign and then I'm creating the ads.
So same thing
to create I click here triggers a web
hook and it starts creating the ads on
the back end.
So we can see so there are a lot of uh
waiting time here. So I'm going to pause
but because the if you create too many
ads at the same time then Facebook at
some point says it's enough. So as you
can see it works slowly but you can just
uh put 100 ads and then it will create
them one by one and then you can go
ahead later and check them out. So if I
go here so this is a old um
ad uh account that I was using. Let me
just find them. Programmative testing
ads set one. And here we have our ads.
Shaky hand steady glow is the picture we
wanted. And you can obviously use the
format that you want and so on and so
forth. So it's for you to decide which
campaign you use, what are the
structures of your adset and what ad you
want to push in each adset. Okay. So
there we go. We have ads running at this
point. So imagine you have 100 ads. Um,
Facebook decides which ones are the good
ones, the ones that resonate with the
customer. You find one or two winners
and then you come back here and you say,
"Okay, those ones are my winners." So,
what's the next step? Again, u I
mentioned it earlier, but you can
iterate. So, if you know that uh this ad
was a winner, then you know that this
angle pushing this USB, it works. So why
don't you just uh create new um
iteration of this? You can use new uh
imaging images uh with the same hooks.
You can use different ways to talk about
this specific marketing angle. But you
can basically iterate again and again to
push the same thing. That is only if you
use static ads. But what if you want to
do more about that? Then this is the
next step. This is a system that is
going to create a mini VSSL or a
textbased uh ad like something longer
that is written specifically based on
the hook that was performing. So, but
basically
we are using u different parameters from
the ones that we have used for the hooks
but some are the same. You still have
the USB that you want to use. You still
have the marketing angle. it was this
one the original hook. So let's say that
was my hook that was performing then I
will create I will take an an ad as an
inspiration. So here's a bunch of ads
that are known for performing. So let's
say I take this one and I want to select
a psychological trigger. Uh let's say
challenge the beliefs and I want to
create a specific emotion into my ads.
Uh, I want to use um design and
inspiration and I want a a bronze spoke
person that is the narrator. I want an
ad that is like 4 minute long and I want
the copyriter David David Ojv to write
it. Obviously, it's just uh to give some
uh clue to the AI and I want to talk to
people that are programmer aware on a
fourth level sophistication market and I
want chat GPT5 to create it. So, I'm
generating it and you will see the
result right away up. It's generating
done. It took only a few seconds. So,
you have the hook, the the lid, the
body, and the CTA. But to visualize it a
little bit better and to modify, then
you can u use that. It's a Google doc.
And this is basically your hook. It
always makes it in a way that's possible
to to speak it. So basically, you can
use this script to create a voice over
with B-roll ad. So no mirror, no
problem. Miracle bomb makes mistake
impossible and glow inevitable. Imagine
never again worrying for your blush when
went on too strong. never panicking
under the harsh office light that you
you can read it yourself. It's an ad
that is um again it can be modified but
this is a very good start that uses all
the parameters that you want and you
have a script you can um you can run
with. What do you do with this script?
That's a good question and as I said
it's still in the building. Uh I'm still
thinking of how we can automatically
create uh the ad with the B- rolls that
are available uh all the videos that the
brand have. Uh not there yet. So far the
only um the best way I found is to use
icon this specific product within icon.
I'll put the link in the description. Uh
but basically it's it allows to import
all your bureaus and just start with a
script. So you just take your script
that was written for you, put it into
this tool and then it will segment it in
different pieces, different sentences
and for each of them it will offer it
will find the the B-roll that you
already have that fits the best to the
specific piece of the script. So you can
have a very fast process. It's not
completely automated yet, but you can
generate uh scripts at scale scale quote
unquote based on specific parameters you
want to test. Take those scripts, put
them into icon and have someone that is
just attributing the right bureau,
creating a voice over with AI and then
write into the the ad account and test.
You can generate like 20 good ads per
day u minimum with a small team using
this method. So that's it for this
video. I hope you found it useful. I
hope it kind of reframed the way you
think of ads and now you don't see that
as a a creative guesswork that is
completely chaotic but instead you see
it as okay we actually can make a system
out of it. We actually can use different
parameters that we can test in a
structured way. So we will we will
logically find the right combination
that works with our customers because
that's is the message I really wanted
you to uh to get in this video. Uh
that's being said that being said uh I
will put in the description. So first of
all uh I talked briefly about how to go
with the gold nuggets and and if this
video that you just watched uh kind of
feel overwhelming you you would like to
create that but not at this level then I
will put in the description a video that
as I said will walk you through a
similar system but if you start from
scratch like if you don't have any uh
real knowledge in marketing then it will
just help you to go from like nothing to
very good copywriting and marketing uh
all at once only using simple LLM no
automation no Google spreadsheet just
simple prompts simple framework that you
follow and for it works for every type
of product business uh even service
business so the link in the description
I will also put the link of templated
and um icon in the descriptions in the
description those are affiliate link so
if you decide to use them it would be
really nice if you could use my
affiliate link. That's all for this
video. I see you in the next one.
Bye-bye.