Hello and welcome. In this video, I'll
show you exactly how you can take any
product and turn it into viral UGC ads
using V3 and Google's brand new model,
Nano Banana. The process is simple,
fast, and repeatable. So, you can test,
iterate, and actually start to create
ads that convert. So, if you're ready to
go, let's get started. Now, to create
our UGC ads, I've broken the process
down to three simple steps. First, we'll
start by picking the product. This could
be something that you already are
selling or just some random product if
you want to practice. I'll show you how
to break that product down into scripts
and angles that actually make sense for
marketing. Next, we'll create the
scenes. So, we will generate images for
our ads. These aren't just random
pictures. We're going to design proper
ad scenes using Nano Banana, which can
create avatars holding products and
looking super realistic. And then
finally, we'll take those images to
generate our videos. Then we'll stitch
them together into complete ads. By the
end, you'll know exactly how to go from
nothing to a finished ad. All created
using Google's V3 and Nano Banana. And
the best part, once you learn this
process, you can repeat it with any
product and scale it up as much as you
want. So, let's get going and start
finding our first product. I just went
to Perplexity and searched what's the
most trending products this month. It
gave me a list and I picked the one that
stood out. So, I went ahead with the
smart water bottles and found a brand
that could potentially be a good fit for
what we're trying to do. So, I did some
research and I found this brand. It's
called Hydrate Spark and it could be
very trendable because they have this
LED light on the bottom and it seems
like a quality product. It's also very
simple to show in someone's hand and it
works well in all settings. That means
we can test a lot of ad angles and try
multiple avatars, which makes this
product a perfect demo. Once we're on
the website, we need to find the actual
product that we want. So, I'll go to
Smart Drinkware and let's try this one.
Once we're happy with the product and
all of the images looks good, we'll take
one or two of the images and just save
them to our bank. So, I'll save this.
And we'll also just get the product
information so we can mark everything on
this side, these drop-own menus to get
as much information as possible about
this product. Now that we have saved the
images and copied the product
information, we're going to paste all of
that information into chat GBT. I also
prepared a special prompt that acts like
an expert product analyzer. So I'll
leave a link for this prompt in the
description. You can just copy this one
and paste that into chat JBT. Just go to
the top and paste that in. And I'll say
here is our product info. Now chat GBT
will break that down into key features,
benefits, pain points, unique selling
points, ideal customer profile,
emotional hooks, and call to actions
ideas. So this will work for our base to
create our ads from. Now that we have
run the product analyzis, it's time to
turn that information into scripts,
avatars, and prompts for our ads. We'll
grab the second prompt I've prepared in
the Google Docs. I'll just copy paste
this one. This way, GPT keeps the
context from our analyzes and gives us
ready to use ideas, image prompts, and
video prompts. All right, so now we got
our custom avatar. This is Kayla. She's
24. We got a little backstory right
here, but we also got the ad scripts. So
you can see the scenes. So here's the
hook, the problem, the solution. And
once you scroll down, we can see the
breakdown with the prompts. So here we
got the script. Then we got the nano
banana prompt. So this will be our image
prompt. Here we got all of the scenes,
all of the scripts, and all of the
prompts that we need to start creating
these ads. The cool thing is that you
can play around here. You can ask chatbt
to create more variants. If you didn't
like the first one, you can ask it to
create like five variants, 10 variants,
as many as you like and then make more
hooks or alternative prompts. And then
you pick a script that you like in order
to create the ads that you want. So, for
now, I'll just stick with this version.
The key is to get the foundation right
because when your first scenes are
solid, then the rest of the process goes
a lot smoother. Let's head over to
Google AI Studio so we can start to
create our images. So just go open
Google AI studio. Inside here you will
find nano banana. So click on this one.
So the first thing we will try is to
create the avatar from the prompts that
we already generated. I'll run one of
those so you can see how it works. So
just go to your chat GBT and find the
nano banana prompt. So let's go for the
first scene and just copy this one and
then we'll paste that in. So, as you can
see, this is okay, but it seems very AI.
So, I will actually show you a useful
trick so that you can find a image
online and use that as your reference
image. It helps AI match the style and
the wibe you're going for. What I'll do
is I'll just go to Hen because I know
they already have a lot of AI avatars.
So, you can use any image if you want,
but I'll use one here. You just click on
create a video. Click on the one in
portrait because that's the one we're
creating and then you go to the avatar
in the top corner right here and then
you click on replace avatar and they
actually got this UGC section. So click
on UGC and then you find the one you
like. I think this one could work well.
So what we do is we just right click and
then we save that image. Once we have
the image, we can go back into Google AI
Studio and we can just add that in and
say, "Please change the hairstyle
and her outfit, but keep the same
quality." Let's run that one. Now, as
you can see, we generated a new image
from this image that we already liked
because we asked it specifically to have
the same quality. Now, this isn't as
polished as some of the images usually
these AIs create. I'll use this image as
our reference image to create all of the
other scenes. Now that we have our
reference image, let's head back to Chat
GPT to pull the prompts for the scenes
that we want to create. Starting with
the first prompt, we can see that we
have a girl in the gym holding our
product. This tells us that we need to
combine both elements, the girl and the
product. We'll copy this prompt and
we'll go to Google AI Studio and we'll
add in our reference image and we'll
also add in our product. Once you add
the product, make sure that it's in the
same format so that Google doesn't get
confused. Now we can just tell Google
make her hold this product in a natural
way. Then we run that. Now we can see
that we have our reference image holding
our product. Now our prompt was young
athletic woman. I'll say put her in the
gym wearing gym clothes holding this
black smart tumbler towards the camera.
And I'll also add keep the quality the
same. Now, let's see how that looks.
We'll keep iterating until we get the
product that we want. This looks pretty
nice, but I don't like that she's
holding it with two hands. So, I'll just
download this again and tell it make her
hold the product with one hand. Let's
see how that turns out. Great. This
looks nice. Now, she's holding it in a
natural way and everything is looking
great. So, what we'll do is we'll
download this and from there it's just
repeating the process for all of the
five scenes. The key is to tune the
prompts until the images fits the scenes
that you want for the ads. So, I'll just
keep going finding the next scene. And
once we got all of that figured out,
we'll download them. Now that we got all
of our scenes downloaded, the next step
is to prep them for V3. We want to make
sure that V3 generates the videos in
portrait format. To keep it simple,
we're going to pre-frame the images
inside of Canva. This step is crucial
because it makes it super easy for
Google AI to understand exactly what
we're asking for. So, just head over to
Canva and inside here, you want to
create a new presentation in landscape
mode. And then you just pick a color.
I'll pick the blue one. Open five slides
for all of your scenes. Then I'll drop
each image right in the center and then
download every image. So, let's head to
Google Flow and I'll show you exactly
how you can turn those scenes into great
ads. Now that we're inside Google Flow,
we'll start by creating a new project.
So, this is the scene builder and this
is where we'll actually generate our
videos. In here, you got a few options.
Click on frames to video so that we can
use the scenes and images we just
created in order to make the AI
understand what we're trying to create.
Make sure you have the frames to video
on. And then make sure you also have the
settings set to V3 fast. We don't want
to waste any credits by using the
quality one. It isn't that much better
and fast also runs a lot faster. So just
upload the image and we'll just click
the crop and save. Nice. Now the image
is uploaded. We'll head back to our chat
GBT and grab the V3 prompt to put in
here. So go to V3. This will be the
first scene. Just paste that in. Make
your adjustments to the script. It isn't
perfect, but with a small adjustments,
you can make it perfect. I'll just edit
this first one to say use the image as
reference. Because V3 doesn't really
create videos in portrait, we need to
make sure that it understands what we're
trying to do. So, what I like to do is
I'll just say only rule is to keep the
blue on the sides as it is. Now, let's
just run this prompt. At this stage,
it's really about testing. You try out
your images with different scenes and
different prompts to see what works.
Some videos just won't turn out right,
and that's okay. I just started to
generate all of the scenes. I'll show
you the first one.
>> Okay, this bottle literally guilt
tripped me into drinking more water.
>> And as you can see, that degeneration
didn't turn out well. You see that
there's something off with her eyes and
she's talking very slowly. So that's why
you need to really play around and do a
lot of generations. I basically swapped
out the image because I didn't like that
one and this one really turns out a lot
better.
>> Okay, this bottle literally guilt
tripped me into drinking more water.
>> That's a lot better than the first one.
And then I just kept experimenting. I
tried to just continue this scene
without her holding the product. This is
how the next scene looked.
>> I would finish a workout and realize I
barely sipped anything. No wonder I felt
so wiped out.
>> So, the whole point here is just to
generate videos, review the results, and
basically mine the best content. If you
look for the moments that stand out,
those become your core ad. I tried with
this image.
>> I have this smart water bottle. It glows
when I forget to drink. every sip.
>> But as you can see, this wasn't the best
generation. So, I just switched the
scene again.
>> Now, I'm actually hitting my hydration
goals. And honestly,
>> and then I tried a new scene with the
same prompt.
>> So, I grabbed this smart water bottle.
It literally glows when I forget to
drink, tracks every sip I take, and even
syncs to my phone. If you're into
fitness or just struggle to stay
hydrated, this one is a lifesaver. Once
you have your generations, just bring
them into your favorite editor. For this
demo, I used Canva and I downloaded all
of the clips that I liked. Finally, I
stitched them together into a complete
ad. Now, I wish you the best of luck
putting together your own. Here's how
this ad turned out after the editing.
Okay, this bottle literally guilt
tripped me into drinking more water. I
would finish a workout and realize I
barely sipped anything. So, I grabbed
this smart water bottle. It literally
glows when I forget to drink, tracks
every sip I take, and even syncs to my
phone. If you're into fitness or just
struggle to stay hydrated, this one is a
lifesaver.
>> I hope you got some value out of this
video. If you did, make sure to hit that
subscribe button. This is a brand new
channel and we'll be sharing a lot more
content in the future. I'm wishing you
the best of luck creating your own
generations. And if you need any help,
just reach out and we'll see if it's a
great fit. Thank you so much for
watching. Have a great day. Bye.