Okay, so I just tested something that
completely blew my mind. I took viral
videos from Tik Tok and recreated them
with AI for different products in
literally minutes. No film crew, no
models, no editing, just AI doing
everything. And the results, I honestly
had to watch them twice because I
couldn't believe they were AI generated.
Look, I know what you're thinking right
now. This probably needs expensive
software, editing skills, maybe even a
whole production team. Wrong. What I'm
about to show you requires absolutely
zero experience. Here's why you should
listen to me. I've been testing AI video
tools for over a year now. I've seen
what works for viral UGC content and
what's just hype. So, when I tell you
this tool is different, I genuinely mean
it based on real experience. Here's
exactly what you're getting in this
video. I'm testing Top View video agent,
which is powered by OpenAI Sora 2 with
three completely different real
products. You'll see the full recreation
process from start to finish.
Side-by-side comparisons that'll make
you question what's real anymore, and my
completely honest reaction to how
insanely good this has become. Let's get
into it. If you want to follow along,
head to topview.ai, link in the
description, click try video agent, and
you're in. The workflow is stupid
simple. You need just two things. An
image of your product and a viral
reference video you want to recreate.
That's it. Upload those two things and
the AI handles everything else. Let me
show you what happens behind the scenes
because this is where it gets really
interesting. For my first test, I went
to Colada, a platform that tracks which
products are crushing it on Tik Tok
right now. It shows you which videos are
getting the most sales, which creators
are converting the best. I found these
jeans that were absolutely crushing it
this week. Then I grabbed a video from a
creator whose content was converting
like crazy based on actual sales data. I
uploaded the jeans photo as my product
image and her video as my reference. You
choose portrait or landscape format
depending on your platform. I went
portrait for Tik Tok. Now watch what
happens. The AI starts creating what
they call a smart plan. On the left
side, you can see it working through
different stages. First, it analyzed
your product just from the photo. It
creates a full comprehensive list of
features automatically. For these jeans,
it picked up the wash, the fit, the
style, all just from the image. Then it
writes an entire video brief with an
outline of what the video should be
about, who the target audience is, and
the key selling points. Next, this is
the genius part. It analyzes why the
reference video actually worked. It's
not just blindly copying. It's
understanding the psychology behind it.
For this video, it picked up hooks like
viral bloat friendly jeans and Mother
over 40 as strong attention grabbers. It
identified specific shot types,
close-ups highlighting the stretch,
moments expressing love for the color
and shape. Then the AI storyboards
multiple shots for your UGC video,
keeping it aligned with what made that
reference successful. Shot one, shot
two, shot three, all planned out
automatically. You review the
storyboard, click proceed, and the video
generates. The AI creates each shot
separately and edits them together. When
this finished, I was genuinely shocked.
Stop for a second. Look at this,
>> you guys. I'm not kidding. These are the
stretchiest, most comfortable jeans I've
ever owned.
>> Multiple shots. She's holding the jeans,
showing the stretch on the waistband,
different camera angles, natural
movements. If I showed this to my
parents, they would not know this was
AI. The pacing matches almost perfectly.
The shot types are identical. The
messaging hits the same selling points.
This is all powered by OpenAI Sora 2. I
generated several more versions to test
consistency, and every single one
delivered. different UGC avatars each
time, same professional quality. Because
the AI learned from a video that already
proved it could convert based on actual
sales data, it knew exactly what
language to use, what points to
emphasize. What's even crazier is how
the AI adapts the style. Each version
felt authentic, like a real person
reviewing the product, the hand
movements, the way they interact with
the genes, the natural pauses and
speech. All of it looks and sounds
completely real. The only small thing I
noticed is videos cut off around 12
seconds. So, you don't get the full call
to action, but I'll work on the
prompting for that. For my second test,
I searched UGC makeup on Tik Tok and
found this video for Rebound Skin Milk.
Huge in Australia, sold out everywhere.
It's a milky toner you apply before
makeup. This was the perfect test
because we have a real paid human UGC
video. This creator does UGC
professionally, so we're comparing
professional quality to AI. Here's what
made this tricky. In the video, the
creator applies cream into her hand and
rubs it in. She's physically interacting
with the product. AI has never done that
convincingly before. This has always
been the weak point realistic product
interaction. I uploaded the product
image and her video is reference. This
time the AI gave me a product
questionnaire. It asked, "Who are the
main users? What are the key selling
points? What are your target countries?"
This is smart design. Instead of
guessing if the AI needs more
information, it asked directly. This
ensures the final video is actually
accurate and targeted. I filled it out.
Super hydrating, supports skin barrier,
reduces redness, and hit generate.
Finally got my hands on the viral
rebound serum. It's supposed to be
amazing for sensitive skin.
>> Did you see that? The AI literally
squirted product onto her hand. She's
rubbing it in with natural hand
movements. The product dispensing looks
real. The skin absorption looks real.
That is absolutely insane. Multiple
edited shots flowing naturally.
Realistic movements. The AI picked up
all the key phrases. Super hydrating,
calms redness, strengthens skin barrier,
and incorporated them seamlessly into
the script. Here's what shocked me most.
I generated three versions. The original
mentions it sold out in Australia. Both
AI videos have Australian accents. Is it
picking that up from context? That's
next level marketing understanding
powered by OpenAI Sora 2. It's not just
recreating visuals. It's understanding
target demographics and regional
preferences.
>> Finally got my hands on the viral
rebound serum. Everyone's talking about
this for barrier repair.
>> Okay, let's try it.
>> That delivery, that pacing, the
conversational tone. This is completely
ready to post. You could run this as an
ad right now and I guarantee it would
perform well. For my third test, I use
my actual product, my ice tub. The
reference video breaks down five
benefits of ice baths. Burns fat,
improves mood, strengthens immunity,
fights anxiety, reduces soreness. I
uploaded my ice tub image and the
reference. The AI recognized five
distinct benefits, so it created five
different shots automatically, smart
enough to structure the video based on
the content breakdown.
The AI filmed someone pouring ice into
an ice bath, taking the lid off, getting
into it, multiple complex actions,
realistic physics with the ice and
water, natural human movements showing
the actual use case. When could you
imagine AI would choreograph and film a
sequence like that, understanding not
just what the product looks like, but
how it's actually used in real life. I
never thought that day would come this
soon. Shot composition matches. Message
structure is identical. The educational
tone is preserved. Quality is scary
good. All powered by OpenAI Sora 2. Now
for the curveball. I wanted to see if
Topview agent could handle something
beyond physical products. So I gave it a
screenshot of my website tools deck.ai
and AI tools directory. This is
completely digital. No physical product
to hold, no texture to show, no
unboxing, just a website interface. If
the AI can market this effectively, it
can truly handle anything. For
reference, I used a tech reviewer
breaking down a new laptop. I wanted
those tech vibes, that enthusiastic but
informative presentation style that
works well for digital products.
>> Finding the right AI tool is a nightmare
until I found tools deck.ai. It's a
directory of the best AI tools, all
curated by experts.
>> Look at this. It's making motion
graphics, professionallook animations,
text flying in, screen transitions that
look professionally edited, visual
elements highlighting different features
of the website. This went way beyond
UGC. The AI understood this is a digital
product and created actual tech
marketing content with professional
motion graphics. It adapted its entire
approach. That level of contextual
understanding is genuinely impressive
and shows how versatile this tool really
is. Here's the final compilation. All
three tests side by side. Original viral
videos versus AI recreations with top
view video agent. Look at these
comparisons carefully. Can you honestly
tell which are originals and which are
AI recreations without me labeling them?
That's the real aha moment here. It's
genuinely becoming hard to distinguish
AI generated content from human created
content. Good AIGC content is officially
here, not coming in the future. Not
something we'll have access to
eventually. Right now, today, I'm going
to be honest, part of me is genuinely
scared by how real this is getting. This
is getting too realistic too fast. I've
had people send me Sora two videos over
the past few weeks asking, "Is this real
or AI?" Because they literally can't
tell anymore. But here's the reality.
This technology is here whether we like
it or not. You can choose to resist it
and eventually get left behind or you
can embrace it. Learn to use it
responsibly and let it help you create
better content faster. For businesses,
this genuinely changes everything. Think
about what this means. Top view video
agent lets you recreate any viral video
with your product in minutes. No
production crew to hire, no editing
skills required, no expensive equipment
needed, just your product image, a
reference video, and AI does all the
heavy lifting. The smart analysis built
into the tool understands scripts,
pacing, camera angles from the original
viral content. It figures out why that
content worked and applies those same
winning principles to your product. The
workflow is completely effortless. You
go from trend discovery to
productionready content all in one
place. Made specifically for e-commerce
brands, marketers, and content-driven
campaigns. You can test multiple
variations quickly. See what resonates
with your audience and scale what works.
That's the real power here. The ability
to iterate and test at a speed that was
impossible before. Want to test this?
Head to www.topview.ai
link in description. Check the pack
opening experience on the site to redeem
it and start creating your own viral
video recreations. But real talk, does
this excite you or scare you? Are you
team AI is replacing everything and
that's terrifying? Or are you team this
is the future and we should embrace it?
I'm honestly somewhere in the middle and
I think that's where most of us should
be. There are aspects of this technology
that genuinely excite me. Think about
the possibilities for small businesses
who couldn't afford professional video
production before. a local coffee shop,
a handmade jewelry brand, a fitness
coach just starting out. They now have
access to the same quality content that
major brands were spending thousands of
dollars to create. That's powerful. The
ability to test ideas quickly before
investing heavily is another game
changer. You can try 10 different video
concepts in a single afternoon, see what
resonates with your audience, and then
double down on what works. That kind of
rapid iteration was impossible before
without burning through massive budgets.
And there's something beautiful about
the democratization of content creation
tools. We're removing barriers. We're
giving people who have great products
and great ideas but limited resources a
real fighting chance to compete in the
digital marketplace. But I'd be lying if
I said I didn't have concerns because I
do. The potential for misinformation and
deep fakes is real and it's scary. When
you can create videos this realistic
with just a few clicks, how do we
maintain trust in what we see online?
How do we protect people from being
manipulated or deceived? The challenge
of distinguishing what's real from
what's fake is only going to get harder.
We're approaching a point where our
natural human ability to detect AI
generated content is going to fail us
completely. That has serious
implications for everything from
journalism to legal evidence to personal
relationships. And I think about the
impact on creative professionals who
make their living creating this type of
content, the UGC creators, the video
editors, the production teams. These are
real people with real skills who built
careers in this space. What happens to
them when AI can do in minutes what took
them hours or days? That's not a
hypothetical concern. that's happening
right now. I don't have all the answers
here. Nobody does. This technology is
moving faster than our ability to fully
understand its implications, but I think
the conversation is important. We need
to talk about both the opportunities and
the risks. We need to think about how we
use these tools responsibly. We need to
consider the human impact alongside the
business benefits. So, drop your honest
thoughts in the comments. I read every
single one and would genuinely love to
hear different perspectives on this
because it's a complex topic with no
simple answers. Whether you're excited,
scared, skeptical, or optimistic, I want
to hear your take. Let's have a real
conversation about where this technology
is taking us. Now, if you want to become
a millionaire this year, watch this
video right