Hey clothing brands, Google's V3 is
about to kill traditional video
marketing. We're talking about 8second
cinematic stylized sound enabled videos
from a single text prompt. You type it
in and Google VO makes it real. It's
like having your own literally Hollywood
director, VFX team, audio engineer all
rolled into one little prompt box. And
yes, this is real. Hey, my name is
Christian Pñan, one of the co-founders
here at Bit Branding. We're specialized
in helping clothing brands scale online
and we've served over 300 clothing
brands in the last year alone. I would
appreciate it if you like and subscribe
so you don't miss any of our content.
Now, let me show you exactly how to use
VO3 to create viral videos that sell
your clothes like crazy. So, step one,
you really want to understand the power
of VO3. Most AI video tools out there
just create kind of like the visuals,
right? But VO3 goes a step further and
it generates native audio. It generates
realistic camera motion and video scenes
that follow your instructions like a
trained cinematographer. So you can
create Tik Toks with storyline hooks.
You can create Instagram reels with
product reveals, cinematic B-rolls for
paid ads and create UGC style scenes
with humor and dialogue. Really the best
part about this is that you can do it
all in dur.
And speaking of prompt, I think that's
the the biggest crutch I would say with
with Google's video is that you
definitely need to master the prompt
formula. And here's the secret sauce.
You need to write your prompts like a
mini movie script. So the better your
prompt, the better your video. And just
to show you an example, if I type in a
model walks down the street wearing a
jacket, it's going to give me a very
simple video of a model walking. She
actually doesn't even have a shirt on.
It's just a jacket, which is
interesting. And then listen to this.
Hopefully you can we can get the audio
in here.
>> This jacket just makes you feel so
powerful when you walk down the street.
>> For whatever reason, it added that audio
on top of it just saying this jacket
makes you feel so powerful when walking
down the street, which I guess is that's
fine. It's okay. But again, you get an
idea, right? A very simple prompt will
kind of get you there, but it won't get
you to where you truly want to go. Right
now, if we do a different prompt,
something with a little bit more
structure. So, a confident young woman
with natural curls wears a cropped
caramel puffer jacket and distressed
denim. She struts through a bustling
downtown street at golden hour. The
camera follows from a low angle in slow
motion. Sunflares bouncing off glass
buildings. Style is cinematic, warm
tones. The audio upbeat R&B instrumental
plays faint city sounds. Her heels
clicking on the pavement. And this is
the video that we got from that one.
>> The music could be a little bit better,
but we have all the right elements in
here, right? We have the right model
that we want. We have the camera angle
that we want. we have the the tones and
the color palette that we want from that
video. So, you kind of see the
difference. Now, when it comes to
structure of your prompts, these are the
things that I want you to include.
Number one, it's going to be the
subject, right? Who is in this scene?
Number two, the action. What are they
doing? Number three, context. Where and
when it is happening. Number four is
motion. How does the camera actually
move? Number five, style. So, what
visual tone or genre you want to
emulate? Number six, framing. A wide
shot, a closeup, etc. Number seven,
constraints, right? Are there any
musthaves or things that you don't want
to include? And number eight is audio.
What should we hear? Now, a little trick
that you can use is use those eight
elements and feed them into chat GPT to
actually level up your prompts a lot
easier. So, you don't have to come up
with, you know, all these chat GPT to
actually level up your prompts. And you
can give it kind of like the scene that
you're trying to come up with. So you
can literally have ChadBt come up with
all the details, right? It's a little
bit of cheating, but look, we're all
doing it right now, right? So you can
use ChadBT to expand your base idea. So
you can start with something like, give
me a cinematic scene for a male model
wearing street wear in an urban setting,
right? Then you tweak the results. You
add sounds, adjust framing, describe the
lighting. You got to really think like a
director to some extent. Another bonus
that you can also do is before going
into VO3, you can use chat GPT or
MidJourney or any other image generator
and use the prompt, but instead of a
video, you're doing an image. So, at
least you can get a preview of the look
and really lock down the style down in
like the style references, right? So the
the you're building out the prompt, but
before you feed it into Gemini, you can
actually create images. So you'll be
able to tweak the prompt without using
credits or wasting a prompt on Gemini.
Now, I want you to remember this. You
only get 8 seconds out of these videos.
So you really want to use them wisely.
And to be honest, a lot of what you will
probably be using this, especially as
you're starting to to test it out,
right, is to use them as hooks, right?
is to hook the viewer in the first two
seconds. So, this is where you really
got to think about motion, contrast,
maybe humor, maybe a little bit of
mystery in there because then you can
combine that with something else. So,
for example, like you could do like a
skateboarder wearing a cargo joggers and
it does a trick over a puddle in slow
motion, right? The water splashes,
reflecting city lights, some night mode,
maybe some neon aesthetics. Audio is
maybe some hip-hop bead, the wheels
rolling, the splashing, right? That's
visual. That's visceral. That's like an
instant like thumb stopping content that
you would see on Tik Tok or or
Instagram. Now, this should enable you
to create variations of ads also very
fast, right? Because it can just create
something and I mean one to two minutes
after the prompt and you have this video
already generated for you, right? So,
let's say you want to promote a new
embroidered hoodie like don't make just
one video, right? make five with the
same product just different angles
aerial drone style of the model running
on a rooftop like maybe slow pans
across, you know, hoodie details with
rain in the background. Two friends
wearing the hoodie laughing in a cafe,
right? Again, skater jumping a stair,
you know, while wearing the actual
hoodie. Close-ups of stitching as the
wind moves the fabric, right? The
opportunities are really endless when it
comes to to the content that you can
create and allows you to test widely
ranging ideas and very different ideas
with just a few prompt variations. And
you can create basically new ads to
test. There's no reissues, no extra
models, no nothing. It's just prompting
it just slightly different here. You can
also pair up these V3 videos with actual
UGC. And that's I think a very killer
combo that I don't I haven't seen a lot
of people do. But you can start with
something that is I mean what you see
every day now on social media, you know,
with this AI videos that are very
eye-catching and maybe you're showcasing
that person wearing the product, but
it's a very eye-catching thing. And then
you cut into maybe a real customer
testimonial or review or ending with
your brand's visuals and call to
actions, right? That combination of
using the V3 videos as the hook could be
a very interesting way to to do ads on
social media and also to just to create
content. I think a lot of people tend to
struggle to create new content for just
regular posting. But using this would be
just a very easy way to again just test
different things and see what resonates
with your audience. Now I will say what
we've been showing you so far here is
Google's Gemini. So Gemini has the
ability to insert the the video
component of it. So it's a a very easy
and and what you've been used to
probably using with Chat GPT, which you
just click on video down here. You
describe your video and you could even
add photos in here. So I want to show
you an example of a prompt that we did
adding this sweatshirt as a product that
we wanted the model to wear. And you're
going to be surprised because it looks
awesome. So in this one it was just yeah
black model with t twist out hair
wearing sweatshirt and I put in
parenthesis image uploaded neon lit
Tokyo alley rainy night walking past
glowing signs slow motion camera follows
from behind a cinematic bokeh 24 frames
per second dark synth wave lightning and
then you can add the image of your
product into any prompt that you create
in order for that model to actually wear
that item. And this is the result.
Amazing, right? So, you can create this
right now. This literally took me 2
minutes to make this happen. The beauty
of it obviously is that you get an
opportunity to download this video and
then again you definitely want to
combine this with potentially other
scenes with potentially other content
maybe real content from your customers
and that's where the real magic happens.
Now this right here using Gemini we're
actually under a Google Workspace
account. So we have the pro enabled but
even with the pro there are limitations.
We've already reached the limit today on
creating videos. we have to wait till
tomorrow 8:00 a.m. in order to keep
creating videos. So, just know that us
as a pro account, we were able to create
about three videos and we've kind of
reached the limit for the day. I say
four videos and we reached the limit for
for the day. Beyond this, you can also,
you know, go into the next, which is the
AI, Google AI ultra is what they call
it, which obviously you get a bunch more
credits in the back end. Now, beyond
using Google Gemini, you could also use
Flow. So, this is a little bit newer,
but again, it uses the same technology.
It uses VO3, but with Flow, which I I'll
I'll warn you right now, we don't have
access to to this just yet because we
haven't upgraded our account. But with
Flow, what it allows you to do is be
more of a almost like a filmmaker. So,
if your plan is to potentially create a
a series, right, that you will upload as
Instagram reels and it's following this
character that you've created and this
character maybe goes on different
adventures and different things and you
want that consistency of that character
and sort of like this storytelling
aspect that maybe you're doing it to
entertain again, not necessarily
yourself, but to entertain your
audience. Doing something like that
would be a really great idea and very
easy to do with something like Google
Flow because Flow allows you to have
different scenes and cut up the scenes
together. It almost has like a like a
mini cap cut, you know, already built in
within here and allows you to combine
different scenes. It allows you to stay
consistent. It allows you to by default
add all the elements that you want. So,
we're talking about your product shots.
If you already have a model created, you
can add the model and it it it gives you
that consistency, that seamlessness and
still that cinematic look overall. So, I
would say this was made by filmmakers
alongside with Google to help generate
almost like mini movies, right? But you
can use it to do those types of things.
So, if you're interested in this,
obviously with this one, you will kind
more than likely have to get into the
the AI Ultra, which $125 a month. That's
for 3 months. They're doing a little
sale right now. If you're seeing this,
the the pricing may change, but using
that Google AI Ultra will give you all
these additional tools and you could
even create better content overall.
Again, it's still using the same
technology, but with Flow, you have some
additional tools to potentially create a
longer, you know, more than the 8
seconds, right, that we can create with
just Google Gemini. Hold up just one
second. I want to say if you are a
clothing brand owner and want to jump
into the specifics of your brand and how
to grow it profitably online, you can
schedule a free 45minute strategy
session with us. There are limited spots
so go find a time right now in the link
in the description below. So if you are
a oneperson shop or running a 10person
creative team, VO3 gives you prolevel
content at zero production cost.
Obviously, there's a little bit of cost
associated, but comparing it to what it
would cost you, right, to do those
things. The future isn't about replacing
creative, it's about supercharging them,
right? So, the best brands will use
tools like VO, not just to make videos,
but to help them tell stories that
actually move people, right? So, if
you're serious about growing your
clothing brand, this is the moment to
lean into AI video. Everyone else is
going to run past you with these tools
if you don't learn today. Now, if you're
interested in what other tools are out
there, I would say Higsfield is another
great video tool that you need to know
about. So, check out that video here
next.