Are you tired of boring ads that nobody
watches? What if you could turn a single
product image into a jaw-dropping
Hollywood level commercial using just
one free JSON prompt and Google VO3? In
this video, I'm giving you five AI ad
styles you can copy right now. Your
product image plus JSON prompt equals a
viral video. These ads are not
templates. They're fully cinematic, AI
generated, and ridiculously easy to
create. No editing, no animation, just
results. Watch closely. I'll show you
how to plug your product into each style
and generate complete JSON prompts ready
to paste into Google VO3. Let's go. If
you're ready to scale your brand, grow
your channel, or start your own AI ad
agency, make sure to like, comment, AI
ad VO3 Jason prompt below and subscribe
because we drop tools and templates that
make you money. Here's what you're about
to learn. The five viral ad formats that
work best with Google. Veo3. How to use
any product image with a smart JSON
prompt and how to paste it into Google
VO3 to generate a cinematic video ad.
All free. You'll walk away with
plug-and-play prompts and a proven
structure that works for physical
products, software, food, and more.
Google VO3 is one of the most powerful
texttovideo AI tools right now. Designed
to create full 1080p or 4K cinematic
videos from simple JSON prompts. and the
secret weapon. You can attach a product
image, describe the scene, and the AI
will handle the camera movement,
lighting, cinematic angles, and editing.
V3 turns your product into a movie
trailer, a viral food reel, a realistic
demo, or even a Tik Tok style trend ad,
all with one structured prompt. And
today, I'll give you five proven types
of AI ads, so you never have to guess
what works. Wait, before you spend
anything, here's a quick hack. If you
sign up right now, you'll actually get a
one month free trial. And if you're a
student in certain countries, you can
even unlock 12 months completely free.
But let's say you want to test another
AI video generator like Hiluo, Runway,
Cedence, or Cling AI without breaking
the bank. I found a super affordable
tool that packs insane value. For just
10 bucks, you get access to an
all-in-one platform that combines the
best AI video generators, text to image
tools, and even chat bots, all under one
roof. I'll drop the link and a full
step-by-step video tutorial in the
description so you can jump in and start
creating your AI ads today. All right,
let's jump into the first ad style from
my template, the cinematic showcase ad.
Think of this like a movie trailer for
your product. It's that dramatic slow
motion reveal you'd see in a luxury
brand commercial. Perfect for gadgets,
electronics, fashion pieces, or even
high-end perfumes. The goal here is
simple. Create emotion. We want rich
colors, ores, lens flares, maybe rain or
fog in the background with music that
makes the product feel larger than life.
Here's what you'll need before you
start. One clean product image, your
brand name and tagline, and an
atmospheric vibe. Think neon lights,
sunset, or even light fog. For example,
in this tutorial, I use an imagine
showing off a smartwatch by Lux Chrono1,
a high-end black titanium wristwatch
with glowing dials. This is a cinematic
shot of a luxury black titanium
wristwatch on a marble pedestal.
Dramatic lighting with blue glow, smoke
and background, 4K product photo. Now,
let's talk about the prompt strategy.
Here's exactly what you can tell
ChatGpt. Create a JSON prompt for a
cinematic slow motion ad showing a
product image smartwatch under rain with
neon lights rotating in the air with
fog, lens flare, and emotional music.
Add zooms, panning shots, and a dramatic
tone. I've already prepared everything
for you. Just copy and paste this into
chat GPT. Drop in your product image,
hit enter, and you're ready to go. Once
you've got that JSON prompt, head over
to Google Vo3. Choose the frames to
video option. Then paste your JSON
prompt into the text box. Upload your
product image. And boom, you've got
yourself a product ad that feels like a
Hollywood feature film. You don't need a
new photo for every ad. You can actually
use the same product image to test out
different visual styles. Let me show you
with one of the other five styles. Just
copy the JSON prompt, ask ChatGpt to
generate the full version, then paste it
into Google VO3. The results are
seriously impressive. And here's a
little bonus for you. The first extra
style is the sealed box reveal.
Normally, this type of ad would cost a
lot if you hired a professional, but now
you can generate it instantly. On top of
that, there's another bonus style. A
fancy movie inspired cinematic ad.
Perfect for making your product look
like it belongs on the big screen. And
here's another result using the same
Jason prompt, this time with the
Astroflow air bike. It looks incredibly
realistic, like a sleek electric bike
built for both speed and mountain rides.
Next up, this one's for all the food
lovers. The foodie viral ad. You've
probably seen these on Tik Tok or
Instagram. those mouthwatering food
clips that make you instantly crave a
bite. This style works perfectly for
restaurants, recipe videos, or even
packaged snacks. The goal here is to
make your audience taste the product
through the screen. That means slow
zooms, sizzling sound effects, melting
textures, and close-ups that show every
detail. Here's what you'll need to
create a viral ad for your food product.
A highquality image of your food
product. Optional extras like sauce
pouring or a close-up bite shot for
extra impact. For example, I use and
imagine a juicy burger, cheese slowly
melting, steam rising, a bite in slow
motion, and sizzling sound effects to
seal the deal. That's the kind of shot
that goes viral fast. By following this
tutorial, all you need to do is copy the
food ad style, paste it into chat GPT,
attach your food product image, and hit
enter. You'll get a complete JSON prompt
ready to use for your campaign. Once
you've got your JSON prompt, just drop
it into Google VO3, upload your burger
image, and suddenly you've got a food ad
so good your viewers will be craving it
instantly. Simply swap in your food
product image and you'll get appetite
triggering cinematic style food ads.
Now, let's move on to one of the most
powerful and high-converting ad styles,
the product demo ad. This type is all
about showing your product in action. No
fluff, no mystery, just a clear,
realtime demo that builds trust and
makes people feel confident about
buying. It works especially well for
home gadgets, physical tools, or
e-commerce products. The goal here is to
highlight exactly how the product works,
using clean transitions, and realistic
settings so viewers instantly understand
its value. I've designed a readytouse
JSON prompt for this ad style. Just copy
it, paste it into chat GPT along with
your product details. Then take the
completed demo ad prompt and drop it
into Google Vo3. Upload your product
image and you'll instantly have a
polished, professionallook demo ad that
builds trust and converts viewers into
buyers. And check this out, another
product demo ad created in just 2
minutes. All it takes is a single
product image and VO3 instantly
transforms it into an engaging video
demo ready to use for your channel or
marketing campaign. Up next, we've got
the unboxing ad. The goal here is to
simulate a realistic unboxing
experience. Viewers get to see the
packaging, the reveal, and each item
being pulled out step by step. Add in
some close-up shots, and you've got a
mini story that keeps people hooked
until the very end. And now you know
exactly how to create a complete
unboxing ad that perfectly matches your
product image. Once you drop your
product image and this prompt into
Google VO3, you'll instantly have an ad
that feels like a short unboxing film.
Perfect for tech gadgets, mystery boxes,
or beauty products. And finally, let's
wrap it up with the trend style UGC ad,
but with an AI twist. Think of those
viral Tik Toks, reals, or influencer
reviews you scroll past every day. This
format lets you recreate that authentic
userenerated vibe without needing to
hire creators. The goal here is to make
your product feel like it's part of real
life. A casual moment, a quick review,
or a lifestyle clip that blends right
into social feeds. Once you've got your
completed VO3 JSON prompt for your
product image, drop that into Google Vo,
attach your product image, and you've
got a UGC style ad that feels authentic,
natural, and perfect for Gen Z brands.
UGC focused stores or organic Tik Tok
traffic. Now you're probably wondering,
do I need to learn JSON prompt for this?
Nope. You just one, choose one of my
five cinematic Hollywood level ad types.
Two, attach your product image. Three,
ask chat GPT for a full JSON prompt
using the format I showed you in this
tutorial. Four, copy and paste the
completed JSON prompt into Google VO3.
Five. Upload your image in the asset
section though the frames to video
section. Hit generate and Google VO3
will give you a cinematic ad in one two
minutes. Which ad style will you try
first? Comment below. Number one for
movie style, number two for foodie
cravings, number three for product demo,
number four for unboxing, number five
for UGC trend. And if you'd like to grab
five readytouse JSON prompt ad templates
for Google Vo3 imagetovideo generation,
just drop the phrase imagetovideo JSON
prompt ads in the comments and I'll
share the free download link with you.
Now you've got the exact ad styles top
marketers are using and the tools to
create them yourself, completely free.
If you found this helpful, make sure to
hit that like button, subscribe for more
AI shortcuts, and check the pinned
comment for free tutorials, plus bonus
prompts that can save you tons of time
and money. This is how you out market
your competitors without spending
thousands on ad teams. Thanks for
watching, and I'll see you in the next
one.