15,000 from a single UGC ads created in
bailout 3. That's not the theory. That's
what happening right now with the AI
powered UGC [music] ads on X.com. Users
are posting where the creators share
real numbers from the AI UGC ads that
quietly printing cash for brands. For
example, this guy tweeted that he has
created UGC AI generated ad campaign
that made over $1 million in sales just
with a single ad. Also, users mentioned
that UGC [music] content creation became
super cheap. Instead of paying from $1
to $500 for a single creative, you can
spend [music] from $1 to $10 instead and
create UGC content just in 30 minutes.
So right now, UGC [music] ads with AI is
so simple that literally anyone can do
that. The real challenge is not whether
you can generate the video. It is about
how to make it so that it will look real
and people will buy. In this video, you
will learn how to create high converting
UGC ads using Nana Banana Pro together
with B3. So you can copy paste this
strategy to [music] almost any product.
All right, without further talking,
let's dive in. All right, the first
thing that we have to do, we need to
identify or to choose the product that
we would like to advertise. In my case,
after my own research, I decided to go
with the facial cleansing brush two in
one silicon face mask. And I already
knew that basically this is the product
that I will be able to sell in the
social media, right? And to create the
UGC content. Once you identify the
product, the second step is to make
marketing analysis right and for this
purpose in order to understand who is my
audience and which kind of the pain
points my audience have I use the chat
GPT. So what you can do you can find the
product or you can write the description
of the product in my case I just due to
the thing that I found my product on the
Amazon I just inserted the link and I
started with the easy prompt. So you're
just saying that you are professional
marketer and now your task will be to
create a script for the a UGC ad. Here
is the product and that's it. And
afterwards the charge GPT made the
analysis and started to tell which kind
of audiences we going to work with. And
the first party was the primary audience
the skincare savvy woman from 18 to 35.
It key traits was like the actively
watches the skincare tutorials on Tik
Tok or Instagram. Enjoys trending beauty
gadgets and interested in clear pores
and smoother the skin. Prioritize
product that promise visible results at
home and likely to value affordable
alternative to the salon treatments.
Right? So basically they trying to save
the money. another audience. It was the
secondary audience, the men getting into
the groomy, but I even though I didn't
want to go into this one because I
realized that this is the product that
of course easier to sell to the woman.
Right afterwards, it gave me some kind
of other description, but I said that
okay, I would like to have this primary
audience, the skincare savvy woman. And
I also just copy pasted the key points
that I liked that the Charg has created
for us. Okay. So once we know our
audience right and we know the key
points we know to whom we're going to
show the ad which is very important the
second step will be to create the actual
script. So for this purpose once
everything is set and we have mentioned
the key points that we would like to
show in our video we are making the
prompt and asking the chat GPT to create
other us the script and I simply was
saying that can you drop me a rough
scenarios ads first it will be like a
UGC ads in a kind of in the story format
of course the audiences like the stories
right and on the background tools we
will use just a nanab banana pro to
generate a character and VO3 for the
actual video generation we also need to
tell to judge a bt once the system is
going to create us the actual script it
good to mention which kind of tools
we're going to use because like
different kind of AI tools they have
particular limitations and chat GBT
already know about that so it's good to
mention what we're going to use so after
that it has generated me a script and it
was quite long so I was trying to read
it but I didn't see exactly it was not
showing me like in terms of in the text
format that I was not able to understand
clear what it So then I just follow the
suggestion of the chat GPT that it was
requiring to to create me kind of a next
steps and the first option was to turn
this into word for word UGC script and
write the voice over only versions. So
in my case it would be easier to
understand what it was talking about
right so I said okay please go with the
first and the second option and then
right now you can see that we have like
clear the scene number one the scene
number two and we can see the piece of
content or kind of the speech that our
character need to say and it's easier to
read right now. So the first scene it
was why do blackheads never fully go
away no matter what I do. So in already
in this case we're going to tell about
the problem. Then I was getting facial
using strips trying everything. Then we
showing which kind of efforts the person
has made and then it was saying so I
tried this at home blackhead tool and I
found online and I didn't expect much.
So it was just like okay I bought
something and due to the thing that I
tried everything of course I was not
expecting but then literally pulls out
the buildup from my pores without
hurting. We already like showing the
effect and my skin feels way clean and
blah blah blah. So of course that was
the draft scenario and in case if you go
to work with the chat GPT sometimes it
can create good scenarios sometimes not
probably it's not going to be the final
version so you have to fine-tune so it
was a good scratch as the scenario for
the UGC ad that I would like to create
but at the same time I was not able to
imagine everything that's why I started
to have extra conversation with the chat
GPT and finally we came up with the
short script it has included all the
aspects of the analysis of the marketing
analysis that GBT made and it sounded
like this. So, I want to be honest. A
few weeks back, I was really struggling
with the black pads on my face,
especially around my nose area. Okay, so
we identified the problem. Then a friend
of mine suggested this cleansing
blackhead applicator called Rampula.
This is the product name. And then one
more interesting part that during the
conversation I realized that I also can
includes another product. That was the
thing that she also mentioned that it
works really well when you use it with
the cream called Holy Billy. And
actually, that's quite interesting
thing. the Holy Billy. It was about this
uh cleansing balm. As you can see, it
was not the Holy Billy. It was the April
skin. But I wanted to add another trick
to this video. Instead of this brand, I
wanted to include something from my
hats. And I don't know why. Don't ask me
why. This is the first thing that came
to my mind with the tricky mind. It was
the Holy Billy. And instead of the April
skin, I wanted to write this brand. And
for this purpose, I use the Nana Banana.
And this is the AI tool that we're going
to work with the image generation. And
we will spend some time in this tool
within the other section. But if we talk
about exactly about this product, that's
also what you can do. Right? So you can
take this product, the one that I just
showed you on Amazon. You can take the
screenshot of this and uh then you can
simply rebrand it or to put your own
brand. And that was actually quite easy,
right? So I just said, "Okay, so this is
a screenshot. Please replace the brand
and write the Holy Billy." And easy
peasy, we got this Holy Billy. But
another thing, I also didn't want to
keep this hands. And this is kind of
another trick that you can do. You can
ask the nana banana to remove something,
remove the elements and it perfectly
made the job. So I said okay remove the
hand. So just a can will last. Then
another thing as you can see that open
like it opened cream and I didn't know
in case if I would like to use this
product with a cover on that and that's
why I said that put a cream cap and boom
we can see the cream cap. So basically
everything looks natural right then I
said that's quite interesting a prompt
actually in case if you are working with
the product ads and you would like to
see it from different angles you could
say that make a grid of this product
from different angles like three on
three so you can create different kind
of grids and you can set like the
specific number of columns and rows
together and it can give you like
different angles and that's kind of the
example so it's like from the top and
from the angle view so without the can
with the can but let's go back to the
this section so this is the way how I
showed you you and play around with
different products and to put the custom
brands. Then the other part and after
just a few weeks of using them, I
started noticing a real difference.
Okay, we're showing the effects of the
product. My skin feels amazing now.
Super fresh, really clean and my pores
look so much better. So, if you're
dealing with the same black hat problem,
this is definitely something worth
trying. So, we have the script and the
next section will be to generate the
first frames in Nana Banana Pro that
we're going to use in Vo 3 to generate
our videos. Okay, so once we already
have the script and everything is ready,
right? The next step will be to creating
our character, right? There are like few
methods that you can do. So the first
thing you need to do is to go to the
Gemini or to any other tool actually
where you can use the Nana Banana Pro.
So in my case, I use the Gemini. I have
the pro account. But at the same time,
you also can find the alternative ways
how to use the Nana Banana Gemini for
free. Whether you start the chat with
the Gemini and asking, hey, can you
please create me kind of a woman or a
man depending on the your purposes and
then to set up the environment, right?
This is the way how you can create your
character. But another way is that you
can simply go to the internet or to
check some kind of YouTube video where
the UGC creator is speaking and you
already can see the example of the
environment that you would like to have.
My case, I just started to check when in
the internet and I found this lady and
she's sitting in the car. It was really
super great like to have such kind of an
environment that it's not going to be
like a professional right filmmaker who
is filming the lady that's sheically
just put up the phone and started to
film herself and that's just a normal
car. So this is about the audiences that
I wanted to sell my product but at the
same time I didn't want to use this
lady. I wanted to have the particular
environment and I wanted to change this
character. So I just attached the
reference image and I said can you make
a change that this woman 30 years old
and good-looking and blonde lady. Right.
So, it was easy and this is kind of the
result that I got. That's amazing. As we
can see, that's the same car. It's a
blonde lady. It's totally new, right?
She had like a kind of a blue green
eyes. It's exactly that I was looking
for. And the main thing that she doesn't
look the same as this lady. Maybe like
the eyes are quite close to that. So,
for kind of the main character, that's
it. You don't need to make a lot of the
effort once you creating the character.
That was more than enough. Once we're
going to create the video in the VO3,
you will see that that was enough for
the main character. But as you know,
once we creating the video, we have like
two sections or two main elements. The
video is consisting from the A-rolls and
B- rolls. The A-roll is the primary main
subject footage that drives the story.
While B-roll is a supplemental cutwave
footage used to support the narrative,
add visual interest and cover the edits.
So it would mean that once we have the
main character, right? The main
character is going to tell something,
but at the same time, it's good for
making the content more interactive and
interesting for the audience, we can add
some kind of elements that for instance,
she's staying in the bathroom and we
showing the effects how she had the
black hats and then the after effect
once she has used the products that we
have advertised how she's going to look.
So the effects before and after. Okay.
So for the B-roll purposes, I just took
the lady that was generated in the
previous chart and I just opened the new
chart in the Gemini and started to play
around with this photo. The first prompt
that I wrote that close-up woman on the
reference image looking into mirror and
holding a blackhead cleansing and
exfoliating tool and trying to clean her
face. So basically I started to generate
some kind of different scenarios for the
B- rolls and that's the lady was strange
element. That's why I went further and
just detached that please replace the
elements on this one and it started to
look better but still like didn't look
natural. So then I asked something else
and it has started to generate me the
lady that I didn't want to see but at
the same time I just took back the
reference image that I wanted to have
and I said okay replace this woman on
one which is on the reference image
right and after that we started to have
her but at the same time we can see that
she's filming her on the phone and that
someone is filming that she's filming on
the phone which we don't want to see
right because we want to show that she's
doing everything herself including the
filming and that's why I said okay make
the frame so like she's filming herself
so don't show the phone I mean like the
impression that this is the picture
taken by her on the phone and that's
what I got. Right? So basically that
she's doing something. She's trying to
remove her black hats. We can see that
the structure of the face right now is
not in the perfect condition. So it's
like the effect before use of our
product. And then I said now make so
that she's just watching into the mirror
with the arms down. And we could use it
for some other purpose once we
generating the videos. And then I wanted
to make her face closer and add some
more blackheads on her face. So that's
perfectly made photo to show that she
had some kind of like a skin problem and
this is our character. And then another
thing I wanted to show the after effect
once she has used the product that we're
trying to sell. And I said now make this
lady to look back with clear skin face
as on the reference photo but still in
the same bathroom and in the same
t-shirt. And that's what we got. So it's
kind of the same lady but with a
different skin texture. Right. And we
can see that that's basically her and
the Gemini made perfect work. All right.
Once we have created all the images in
the Nanab Banana Pro before we jump in
into V3, the only thing step is to
upscale and to remove the Gemini created
symbols in here. And of course, there
are particular tools on the web that you
can find. But the one that I found
actually it's again like the Google
product and it's again the Nana Banana
Pro, but it's not in the Ji that's
already in the Google AI studio. So you
need to go there in case if you have the
account then basically you can simply
start to use the Google AI studio. And
within the Google AI studio, in case if
we go back to the homepage here, this is
kind of the uh starting page where you
going to start there will be a section
explore Nana Banana Pro. Within this
section, you will see like where you can
start to type in a prompt the same way
as you do in the Gemini. But there will
be a problem that you need to link the
paid API key. So once you go into use
this chat, you will be charged for the
image generations, but in the same time
that's not going to be super expensive.
So as you can see I've been using
multiple inputs and then I got the
multiple outputs and it was not even
sense. So it was even though less and
actually I have another video how to set
up the Google AI studio. So and the link
will appear just actually now. Okay in
case if we go back so in order to
upscale the image we're just copy
pasting the images from the Gemini chart
and here on the right side we can see
that you can set up the aspect ratio.
And in this case due to the thing that
we are making it for Tik Tok or
Instagram right so we are taking the
aspect ratio 9 to6 which is a mobile
phone aspect ratio and at the same time
we can choose the resolution this case
we can use 1K 2K 4K if the image is
bigger of course you're going to pay
higher the price but in our case due to
the thing that afterwards is going to be
for the mobile phone actually the
resolution for 1K is going to be more
than enough so we just taking the photo
and we just saying okay just upscale 9
to six so simple easygoing prompt And
afterwards that's the image. So it's
upscaled and you can see that this is
our woman. We don't see the symbol in
here. And actually I did with every
photo that I wanted to use in the V3.
Once we all set we are ready to generate
the videos. And for this purpose we're
going to use the video generator which
is V3. And in order to use the V3 we can
go to Flow and this is another Google
product that actually was created for
the V3 generations. In order to go to
flow just write flow. And the first page
here you can see that that's going to be
a Google labs flow about. Once you land
here then you just need to uh hit create
with the flow. So once you are within
the flow you can see the section like to
generate a video with the text and you
have like multiple options text to video
frames to video ingredients to video and
to create image and creating an image
that's again Nana Banana Pro that's also
like the place where you can use that
but in this section we actually going to
use the frames to videos and also the
ingredients to video once we would like
to integrate our actual product to
advertise. As you remember, we had the
scripts where we had like the speech.
Once we going to create the video with
the V3, we need to remember that V3 will
generate the clip for 8 seconds. Once
you're going to make the prompt and for
instance, the woman need to talk about
something. Just make sure that the
speech will be for 8 seconds long. And
this is actually the first script that I
have or the prompt that I have wrote.
So, woman in the car is telling on the
camera like recording an Instagram story
or real. And that's the speech. I want
to be honest, a few weeks back, I was
really struggling with blackheads on my
face, especially around my nose area.
The same thing that we had in here,
right? And that's the actual result that
I got.
>> I want to be honest. Um, a few weeks
back, I was really struggling with
blackheads on my face, especially around
my nose area.
>> Look how real is that? Like the texture,
everything like the moves with the
hands. No, like like six or seven
fingers how it was like in the previous
times, like for instance in 2025. And
actually, that was the whole beginning.
What we going to do next? We're going to
use another feature is called skin
builder. So this is the section where
you just go and then you're supposed to
hit plus sign. And once you're going to
hit the plus sign, whether you're saying
that you want to jump to the next
section or you can extend and actually
we need to extend. So we just need to
instead of the eight second clip, we
want to continue the woman to talk about
the story, right? Or to tell the story
that we have created. So we want to
create all the scenes where she's saying
that okay, this is the first eight
seconds. This is the second, third,
fourth, fifth and sixth. And we are
making it till the end. I just started
to create the prompts for the all the
scenes. As you can see that was extended
and then I was saying that she continues
her speech. Then a friend of mine
suggested the cleansing blackhead and
etc. So I made it for all the all the
sentences that we have created. And in
case if I go to the scene builder, I
will show you just one example how it
made the construction.
>> I was really struggling with blackheads
on my face, especially around my nose
area. Um then a friend of mine suggested
this cleansing blackhead applicator
called Rampula.
>> So we can see that she started to tell
about our product and at the same time
there is like not a smooth transition
but in case if we're going to download
this video these kind of a glitches in
between they will be a little bit smooen
and uh you will see that once we're
going to make the video editing part.
But another thing that I didn't like in
here or that I wanted to improve that
she also going to show the product once
she's speaking right and that was a
little bit tricky that in case if you
would like to extend it and write the
video right I cannot attach any products
as you see here or I cannot attach some
kind of reference images. So for this
purpose basically I just went back to
the actual project and then I have used
another feature that's going to be very
interesting in this case. I've been
using the ingredients to videos. So I
used the frame where the lady was
speaking and then I just make kind of
the screenshot of that and at the same
time I have attached this product that
was rampula and I use this feature. So
in order to use that you just hit the
ingredients to video then you hit the
plus sign and then you choose the actual
product that you would like to
advertise. Finally you can add like
three ingredients. So for instance you
have the lady then the product number
one and the product number two. And then
you just hit the bottom and let's see
which kind of video I got. Then a friend
of mine suggested this cleansing
blackhead applicator called Rampula.
>> So it's perfectly made. You see this is
the actual product that I had and this
is the actual ingredient and she showed
it again. All these nails and fingers
everything it is super natural. So this
is the part that we going to use once
the woman is just talking. It's much
better like to show it once she's
showing the product and actually it
looks real. Yes, there is a difference
with the voice but this section we also
going to cover in the next section while
we will make the video editing. So then
I also made the same thing with the
other product. It was this holy bill
cream and it was also naturally shown
and by mistake I also used this prompt
that it was changing the aspect ratio to
16 to9 and be careful that once you're
generating the video just be specific
about the aspect ratio that you would
like to have because it has like the 16
to9 and the 9 to6. So I generated this
one. Then I also generated the after
effect and it was several shots once
lady was using all these products at
home and once she was using the ramula.
So basically I have generated all the
frames related to the A-roll and the
B-roll. And right now let's go to the
next section actual video editing. Right
now I'm in the video editing tool. I'm
in the final cut but you can use the
capcat. It really doesn't matter. And
the first part that I did, I just
combined all these video elements that
we have generated in the VO3 and I added
all this a-roll right when the lady is
still sitting in the car and speaking.
And at the same time, we can see B-
rolls integrated where the woman is
showing the before effects and she's
standing in the actual bathroom. And at
the same time, like the moments she was
using the products also in the bathroom,
she had a mask then she was using the
another product facial brush in order to
massage her face. And then she was
speaking and amazed that her skin was
amazing. And finally, she was showing
also in the bathroom that her skin feels
great and etc. And once V3 is generating
different clip, of course, the voice is
changing. And we need to fix this
problem. So in case if I'm going to tone
on the video with the original sound, it
will sound like this.
>> With blackheads on my face, especially
around my nose area, then a friend of
mine.
>> So you can hear that for for the for the
first part for for this section, the
voice was number one. And for for this
section, the voice was number two. At
the same time, once the woman is saying
something, we can hear actual AI voice,
which we also want to get rid of.
Otherwise, people will not believe that
it's real. And for this purpose, we
actually need the tool 11 laps. So, you
need to go in there. Once I was creating
the video, I didn't pay anything. So, I
was using the free account because
you're going to have roughly like 10,000
credits. It's more than enough case if
you would like to generate multiple UC
clips. There is a section called voice
changer. Once you have made the the
video need to export clip in the audio
format only and once you will have the
audio format of that just need to go to
the 11 labs go to the voice changer and
the first thing that you need to do you
need to hit the voice in order to choose
the voice you need just to go to the
voice section and here to click that and
within this I already pre-saved the
voices that I liked but in case if you
would like to add some more voices you
can go to voices on this section in the
left and here you can choose the
libraries There are like paid voices or
there are a bunch of voices that you can
use simply for free with the free
account that I did and I have chosen
this voice and it sounded like this.
>> Creativity blooms in every season like a
vibrant flower.
>> In my point of view, it sounded very
similar to the voice that was generated
in the B3. So it heard as the UGC
character that we had. So then you just
need to choose the file, you hit open
and then you make the settings for this
one and then you generate the speech.
Then once 11 Labs has created voice then
I just upload it back to my video
editing tool. Then it has started to
sound like this.
>> Struggling with blackheads on my face
especially around my nose area then a
friend of mine suggested
>> so it has started to be better and like
we also can hear that during the
transition section in between we don't
see the difference in the voice. But
then another thing that I have faced
with it was the actual mistakes in the
voice. So in case if we go to hear it
again
>> with blackheads on my face especially
around my nose area. So you could hear
that she's not saying no. She was saying
like no. Then what I did I just created
the captions and then I I just started
to notice all these mistakes where she
was saying instead of especially the BO3
noticed and also the auto caption
generated noticed as socially which is
wrong. Then instead of the nose we can
see no sometimes it might occur you
can't do anything with that in terms of
the occurrence with that but you can fix
that. In order to fix this you can use
again the 11 laps tool. So the first
thing that you need to do, you need to
check all these arrows in the speech and
then you go back to the 11 labs. And
once you are here, you can use the text
to speech and then you can either insert
all the phrases that been pronounced
incorrectly in here or you can just
insert the specific words that been
pronounced incorrectly. And once you are
here, so you basically paste all this
incorrectly text that has been
pronounced by your UGC character. Then
you specify the same voice and then you
hit to generate again. and it's not
going to cost you a lot of credits. So,
in my case, it was just 255 credits.
Then you download this file and then you
go back to the actual editor and I'll
show you that I just started to change
the words or the part of the sentences
where the 11 laps has made the mistakes
and that's one of the example how it
looks.
>> Blackheads on my face especially around
my nose area.
>> What I did so far, I just fixed all
these problems in different parts like
in here, in here and in here. So, it was
like four or three different places
where the I get the speech problem which
I fixed that way. everything almost
ready but there is one more thing is to
add the background noise in case if
you're going to play the voice it still
might sound a little bit like AI and the
background noise can handle this thing
and to smooth this part so it's going to
be much more real so for this purpose I
just found the city sound and it sounded
like this
so we can hear the beeps that she's
really sitting in the car and in case if
I turn on the voice it sound like this
>> a few weeks back I was really struggling
with blackheads on my face, especially
around my nose.
>> Before I reveal the final result and see
this piece of art in action, smash that
like button if this free miniourse just
level up your AI skill. And of course,
subscribe for more AI content creation
strategies and happy creating.
>> I want to be honest, um, a few weeks
back I was really struggling with
blackheads on my face, especially around
my nose area. Then a friend of mine
suggested this cleansing blackhead
applicator called Rampula. Also, she has
has mentioned that it is super effective
with balm called Holly Billy. But
honestly, after just a few weeks of
using it, I started noticing a real
difference. My skin feels amazing now.
Super fresh, really clean, and my pores
look so much better. If you're dealing
with the same blackhead problem, this is
definitely something worth trying.